You call me from the static, between the waking and the fall
I found you in the fractures
Where the menace starts to crawl
Every dream you couldn't finish
Every star you couldn't name
I was already waiting
In the margins of your pain
Psyche's nightmares come alive
Where the beautiful things go to survive
You bring the darkness, I bring the light
Look up from another one of psyches midnight
Casual
I hope you hear me.
I love you.
I love you too.
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right
little bit
Yeah, I'm I can't say I'm I'm a bit sad
but what oh
No, I'm not I'm not gonna tell you but I'm sure you know, but you know
Yes, and
No, no, no, no, no, but a listen listen about tricks. Let me tell you something
Uh, can I I don't know I can send you a picture. Can I send you or on?
Okay, well listen listen to this, you know, I got those baby kitties
My baby kitties came about October last year, right?
had the daddy and the mommy right they like dropped him off at the front door
right they were hanging on my front and my back door I was crazy yeah and they
left him and right and I have the babies right it's midnight many many many
midnight and orange you boy is what I named them the babies well guess what
Thought he you know I see crazy
I call her crazy cookie because I have cookie my cookie my cat's name is cookie, right and
She kind of she's a calico and she has that crazy cookie look like where it's cut in the face
You know what I mean when girls the
Okay, so I call her crazy cookie right because she has these crazy eyes
Anyways, I think that's the mother of the babies and I thought the orange kitty
With the father
Right all these years
anyways, he left right in October a
Flash like of October a
Flash here and I hadn't seen him and I was so worried for him and he just showed up last weekend
Okay
Yeah, and I and it looks so healthy and so good and I was like it with listen with crazy cookie
That's been showing up this whole entire time
Yeah
That's what cats do sometimes cats can uh, you know
Sometimes bad things could happen, but it's like a lot of times they just
No, but there's this white cat. There was this white and orange cat that it was like this big orange cat and then
That weren't you boy. I call him Cinnabon. I called him Cinnabon. Okay, I named him Cinnabon. I didn't know what you know, I
Got my orange you boy. I was like, okay. I'm gonna call you Cinnabon
You're like the originator
He's a fucking huge. He's huge. I can show you a picture of him
I don't know how to do a backstage on the thingy, but I just got a picture
And you can add image if you present if you give the image handy, but it's not on
Comments it'll say it'll say you know
Oh, you see like little people like before your your faces
There's gonna be a box that says present or invite I think or presents will say present
Media there's like a little box next to your no mine says comments recordings and streamed to the audience
Is it do you see the little boxes where that where your picture is?
Like you see like where you know where you when you go backstage, you know that those boxes where people backstage you see those
No, no
Nope. I don't have boxes. I have no boxes. Like I said, backstage, I have comments, recordings, streams to the audience.
Yeah. There's actually like, there should be, I'm going to look at, I'm going to look to see if I can look at it right now, but I don't see, I see a different thing than you see, so I'm going to see if I can see it.
Yeah. I don't see the same thing. I'm on my phone.
Okay. Yeah. If I go to StreamYard, click on StreamYard. Okay. There's the invite link. If I go backstage again.
It should say
Okay, you see on the bottom you see on the bottom, okay, Collins. Okay, I'm looking at
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, I don't see yours. You don't see on the is any pictures
I see everybody's comments now. Oh, no, not the comments like under the under this under the
Picture on the screen the video
Anybody know
We're recording chat. Let's say present or you can hold it says three people. Okay. I
Okay, look at the bottom your little icons, and I think you may be able to share like
You can't on um
Yeah, you can't on this phone
Yeah, you can't on my other phone, but not on this one
the crystal sandwich. Okay. Okay. Yeah, shit. I'm sorry, dude. I
shouldn't even try it. It's okay. But you know what? Um, you
know, I, I do think that's okay. No, but I really, I, I
really, um, I really, really hope you really think, um, avoid
you dead. What do I do?
You fucked with fucking a nasty predator motherfucker that everybody wants to fucking
He's so nasty. No, we want to hurt him. We all want to hurt him!
Well, your sentiment is very much how people were.
They're a little bit...
No, he's sick.
You don't know what this guy is.
You don't know how he treats people, and he is a devil, and you fucking accepted him
into your life.
So, you got something else going on?
You know, someone in the chat doesn't mean I endorse or anything, or there's a lot of
different kind of people in the chat.
I don't know anybody's background.
Anybody can be here in an alt, right?
Know it's like yeah, I just hope that these people are because I fucking I
Actually fucking fuck with you. It's like yeah, I fucking love your personality. I think you're good for this shit
You just got to keep these bad people out of your fucking distance and stop with that fucking dumb shit, dude
Well, yeah, but there's a lot of people that are like even like no you're better than this dumb shit
No, but you're putting dumb shit
No
No, you shouldn't even fucking think no some of the things that you are questioning should not even be questioned
Well, I mean it's like there's a lot of people with a lot of different opinions. I mean, it's like yeah
Well, you know what? Yeah, you know what some people would originally think that maybe you should get
Sliced under each of his eyes so we should know he's a fucking predator
They're doing violence or horrible things to people like I want to like you know kind of end these cycles of violence and hatred and stuff
Oh, I'm saying that the like when like these things happen
You should slice a motherfucker under the eyes so you can always know that they're predators
Okay, what was he in conviction of a crime? What was the crime?
100%
Being a predator
That's well, that's a that's a very general statement like you say like you know exactly was there a crime
He's got more than one how many crimes. I don't know how many you know what it's crazy is that in Arizona?
They don't give a fuck especially if he's like a like fucking
Going back and forth from country to fucking other side. You know how fucking dirty people are
You think it's okay for him to fucking grape other people's grandparents. Oh my god
Yeah, he tried to grape a pair is somebody's grandma
Hi, did you see what he did on the video I sent you?
I sent you a video that had nothing to do with VP because I knew you were gonna fucking play that shit.
I knew you're gonna say some shit about me trying to pull some shit about somebody else
So I knew that the only that fucking thing was a fucking that shit was nasty dude
That guy should go to fucking he needs to go under the jail. We need a fucking he needs to get stoned
Yeah, well we need to
Well, I think Utah they actually have a firing range. I think that's the most like obscure
So you think it's okay for him to want to grape a grandma. You know when he when he tried to
When he was trying to break in that woman's house, he wasn't trying to just break in that woman's house
He was trying to rape her. Okay. Well, I mean it's like I mean it's shocking. He was trying to
No, this is what you accepted! This is what you like!
How did I accept that I asked you some questions?
We didn't get into any grandmother...
RAP but you know it wasn't it wasn't anybody he knew he said he watched her fucking take care of her dogs
Okay, she had a fucking huge fenced in yard. He broke her fucking fence down. He tried to kill her dogs
He shot at her dogs. Okay. He fucking kicked the door down. Are you stupid?
No, I just haven't heard
Well, I mean, how can I know that?
I've been trying my last fucking...
You already knew about the VP shit.
I thought you said you thought that the VP shit was staged.
No, I didn't say that. I didn't say that. I saw it. I thought it was wrong. I thought it was, I thought it was uncomfortable to watch, even though a little bit I saw of it. It was not, I don't think it's right to mess with somebody when they're asleep.
You said you didn't know if it was like, it was for the cameras or not. That's what you said. And that's why I had to...
I can't imagine why Crystal Marie...
I'm sorry.
I can't imagine why Crystal Marie has no man. I can't imagine why.
Crystal, I mean, it's like...
I'm sorry a sick. I don't care sick. It's fine. Whatever you think, you know, it's fine
It's imagine why you have no choice imagine why you still have a pussy in your man
Well, that's true
So, how are you saying tonight? How was your night?
Segment
One thing you can't hear us.
Sig, are you here or are you there?
Hey, but I'm saying that, and what you did
is very fucking disrespectful, dude.
You did some nasty stuff, though.
OK, OK.
I can't say I do nasty shit, too.
But the shit with Kate and the babies and-
Kate and the babies?
What are you talking about there?
Our kids.
You did I did not it was fucking he said it was great. I seen it. I know with that
I didn't even know she had kids. I don't know
That's disgusting. I didn't say anything about her kids. What did I say?
I'm not gonna repeat it, but it was disgusting
Can someone say what I said guys
It just made me sick honestly. It makes me sick. I don't have many kids yet. I don't really care
I don't want to discuss kids and it's like but she was bringing up me saying I'm a bad cat owner and
That I let my cat run away, and I don't be my cat and I let my cat starve. So is that wrong?
Hello
Well, what she was bringing up is that you went to the store and you were not looking for the cat
When you know, it's been like about 10 11 days yet, so also if you ever oh
So she's been here with me
She knows she has a video camera on here something knows exactly when I go out and look and when I call and right
But you haven't though
I have so and I was supposed to be on that doing IRL all the time for this
They can lay everyone's seat with the search and all coming over here with everybody
I'm just saying what the chat is picking up. Okay. This is what the chat is picking up
That doesn't know fucking shit
How about that?
You know what? I agree with that in a sense because Judd doesn't when they go on a group fucking thing
They do fucking tend to look great
They're saying Samans. Oh my god the cats are all
They're all going crazy. They're steering at the wall. No, they do tend to like
Like we don't really know what's going on. I can't say but when one somebody like I'll tell you this is it
like a lot of these people and nobody uh defends me I'll say this so much but uh a lot of people
like these new horrors that are trying to come in like yourself in a sense but you don't know
anything about art history and you try to come in and try to rewrite it as your own and it's not
He doesn't know shit dude
Fucking liar, dude. She don't know shit crystal. Can I address something real quick? Okay important
Okay, yesterday when I had that person on my show and I and I was I was questioning him
Suspiciously and stuff, but he said something I don't control what comes out of his mouth
He said something and I said don't talk about kids and that's all I said
So I don't owe anybody apology for anything. That's what I said
I think she might owe me an apology talking about my family. We're talking about
Way things beyond anything anything beyond that is not even factual
What is it?
What you're saying
It's not factual. Should we play the clip?
Well, we should
Well, could you start with your own discretion?
Sure
Because you started it and Kate would never have and I
I'm telling you she did not you started and it is not nice
Yeah
just by being defensive.
What name did I call her?
Because, listen, that guy is a disgusting person.
Okay, he does not need to be around us humans.
Okay, he doesn't need to be around nobody.
And if you knew any, okay, maybe you don't know,
I don't care if you know or not.
Okay, he does not need to be,
he does not need to be around us.
I don't want to be around that guy.
Nobody needs to be around that guy.
fucking disgusting human. Okay, he's one of the most disgusting person I ever seen on this fucking
entire platform. Okay, he has done the most disgusting things I have ever fucking seen.
Okay, and you let this motherfucker like run the fucking mug. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
I don't really know, and it wasn't your fault. I don't really know, but...
Why am I all of a sudden like, why am I all of a sudden so, because I talked to somebody
and I, I, somebody that I didn't, I know you were feeling very defensive as far as like
it wasn't even him.
You were attacking me, but like how about this, like, um, like, uh, yeah, I frickin.
It wasn't him.
It wasn't even him.
I get it.
It wasn't him.
It was just the defensive feeling.
I get that all the time.
I'm sure Alex didn't I mean Alex has a really Alex came and talked to me on the panel
But you know who sent me the evidence like on a discord
I have no I don't know fucking
My stalker Tony. Oh, I don't fucking know. I don't know. Oh, I don't know either
Well, why would I know?
You're fucking like I give a fuck who Tony is dude
Tony's your stalker because you did weird shit with kids or some something with a car with a tile
Go die. Okay, bitch die
What a fucking
wet brain psychopath
That is crazy. That is fucking crazy
Yeah, hi, don't come back this little
That's fucking still out of pocket. You're that's the same here when it was coming over. So you fucking insane
Wow
Eternal victim. Yeah, I know I'm an eternal victim right Rob. Oh my gosh. Well, you're a victim of being kicked out of the chat. Whoopsie
I'm sorry. No, sorry. She's not over. Why would it be over? You're about to get timed out again, though
And
Benoit, who is actually Tony, your band, okay, and perfect.
Okay.
Yeah, we're not going to be doing that here.
And it's like, where's the link?
It's right here.
What a fucking cut.
See why I like, with a little bit of a, this is, that's like,
that's the kind of.
Cuckoo for cocoa post it kind of adds. I mean, it's NorCal is. Well, I did see NorCal say much shit about me
And I'm on I'm much weaker and all you know, he knows everything about me, too
I guess I know I guess everybody's in my everybody's in my oh, okay, Bob
It's gonna be okay. I'm gonna be
Watching
Thank you so much
thank you so much okay okay yeah we're not gonna be doing that here we're not
gonna be doing that here yay Tony you know everyone everyone shout out everyone
shout out to uh yeah
To outside the door go somewhere else. You know, it's like really go if you don't like this though, like just go somewhere else
I don't understand. There's a lot of freedom. I know but using the cat through the prop right here
Right, you know
Well, you have my other account banned by the way
Streamyard, I didn't
No, I'm streamer. I mean my other
Well, no, that's why you use this
Windsor it was the ground doctor TV James Craig and James Craig that's that's why I go
Yeah
All right, so I'm gonna say this you get mad at me and kick me, but I'm gonna say it anyways
Listen, whatever your channel starts doing
No, and people come over here and they're having fun, right?
Your panels are fun again, your views are good, you seem to do something to sabotage
it.
Honestly, I'm just saying, there's a pattern.
That's all.
And why don't you want to have a great channel and people having fun?
Okay.
Well, like people are offended by Brendan's mere presence.
They are offended by it.
You know that, right?
You know, I'm just saying psyche. That's all it's my show. How about like I well, you can do what you want if you want to
Sabotage your shit. That's fine. It's fun to watch. I can do that, right? You're absolutely right. You can yeah, I can
Maybe I don't imagine Alex like someone on the loser. That's hilarious
Have you though, have you that's why you go on every panel seeking attention your fake crash outs come on
I think you're sick of it. That's why you go to Brunsburg and shake your ass and start twerking because you're so sick of it
Just stop it. You're so foolish it sometimes
Yes, it does
You've been going panel hopping on this crash out tour. It's come off as incredibly fake
Watch watch me to work my ass on bronze birds. Yeah, this is fun
You got Alex McQueen's second you dig every way like if Alex was a true friend. He'd be like psyche
Why are you sabotaging your own shit? What's wrong? What who hurt you where you don't allow yourself to succeed on this?
Bye, have a good day.
No one cares.
Geez.
I mean, I have someone come up here
and just bat my face.
I mean, geez, I let him talk.
That was enough.
He had his word.
He had to say what he wanted, so.
Yeah.
Our crystal city back there, did I pin my link?
I didn't, I mean, geez.
Hey, won't be safe, how are you doing?
I mean, it's like, guys, so just because I don't know all the lore and stuff like that and then I'm being told by like my literal stalker, you know, threatening me about this and stuff like that.
I'm gonna take a step back and go, okay, I don't know what's going on, but I don't believe anybody should be deprived of a voice, you know.
And I'll let us be for 10 minutes
She doesn't use it. Are you guys use me? It's really wet like disgusting shit. Do you hear that?
It's just trolls you guys you guys like you care you just care you're like you're trying to get control
Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Good job. Good job. Good job. My mods. Shut up. Thank you
Yeah, I have I have nobody here day in the day. I mean, it's like I mean it's like I'll do a thing my way, right?
It's like, yeah, at least I'll do my way. I'm not gonna be fucking
Couch out, but she's day. Well, you can see you just said it like five minutes ago before right before she gets up the panel
You know
Just something discussed
You know, be inspired doesn't work. It didn't work
her powers her powers
But wow, maybe it's gracious
I've never
Is they really saying no thing though to me is like, you know
There's something weird
Let me see. It's coming up.
Check.
No. Okay, they left. Okay.
Yeah.
Someone must do a salon. They couldn't do anything for her to be on.
Look at that.
So you're called a horrible man.
They call it food.
Jeez.
What do you think?
Talks about me. I have to let them know or do you kind of use your name?
This is listen to what we don't listen to it. Just leave
It'll sit listen to your voice
G
Fucking my stalkers, too
You did what you know you said to me
No, I'm just playing something disgusting way out. It's like and I said if anyone wants to donate and maybe I'll let her
That's the benefit of having my own show, right? And every other show I can talk all this day what hours and I tried to let that happen on my show
You talk shit about me, like really? I mean I have to listen to it just make it because you're always loud
explain your life to you.
If you didn't do shit, you just don't like granted.
Okay, I know you don't like it, but you're saying, you know, basically,
you know, you know,
you know, torture him, and you relate him,
and then you call him me at PDF.
So, okay.
Leave if you don't like to tap.
Like, really, it's really simple.
If you don't like it, turn it off the TV.
If you don't like it, block it personally.
It's like, why do you have to make me
So I can, you know, click over one thing,
somebody that's never been editing in the chat.
That's my judgment on the effect.
But, wow, I mean, it's like, so,
I mean, I would never go to any show
and do that for them, I mean, I would just,
so I've been thinking for the heart and stuff like that.
I appreciate the love, I see them, I see them,
I appreciate that.
I know I can be on the unpopular side of things, but you know what, I'm used to being
on the unpopular side of things, I'm used to being scapegoated, I'm used to being slandered,
I'm used to being made fun of and bullied, you know, it's happened all my life, so it's
like nothing really new.
So maybe I like will have a little bit more compassion or like, you know, understanding
Not just to take any word for it, you know
Oh here we go
Okay, let's see who's on
Okay, maybe this
Hey, so I hi what radius is serious. What's up? You look a little serious
I look a little serious serious serious. I don't know. So what's going on?
I can barely hear you like seriously your mic. Is it even on?
Is this the one that's much better? Okay.
Barely. So what's happening? Why?
Why are you so upset? Tell me why you're upset. I'm not upset. I mean, it's like I
Basically
Everyone else got very upset and I like you know and basically I was like
well, I
Don't know anything about it. And it's like I didn't really I don't care someone's in the chat
Because they can be under all the I don't I can't look up everyone's background in the chat
If people can always block people personally, but I'm gonna see them at all
And I don't know that person now. I turned into receiving money from him
I'm a staff is never no idea
We look like or anything out of but I'm just like would have people this telling you what to do whichever one's doing about LZ
You ever was doing about several other people and it's like in this thing people
Not even able to defend themselves but having very serious allegations made and I would like to okay
About them. Well, let me ask you because it's been a couple days now from my understanding, right?
Yeah, since all this kind of erupted
Have you
Seen any of the footage that these people are talking about? I
Saw well Alexander played me the beat the beat. She played some on the vegan Patriot stuff on the video
She made and she talked to me about the what happened with being Patriot and that was pretty shocking, but
And I know about yeah, you know, I'm breaking like an old ladies house
And he was arrested and so right
Um, so
Have you seen any of the footage of him just his behavior even when he's not doing those specific things?
Not too much. Like I said, Tony sent me the Tony sent me the videos. I didn't really feel like
Well, lots of people have been playing them. Okay, even if you I just haven't seen them on a show. Yeah, so okay
Well, I didn't know who this guy was before either. Okay, I've heard the name
I've heard him being shit talked before but I didn't really know anything about him either
Over the last couple days when I've had the chance. I've seen some of the shit and
You know these people
Tell me who dad. He's not a good dude or actually telling you the truth
Well, it's the amazing bad dude. He's a terrible person. I still I'm interested in the psychology of
Psychopaths criminals like it seems like you might be a psychopath
Um, you know, it's never a problem for anybody else that does a YouTube show to go into people's minds and to do things and all that kind of stuff, so I don't understand why.
I'm held, I'm called, first of all,
I'm supposed to be part of this community.
I don't know what community it's supposed to be.
It's a bunch of rival factions of gangs.
It seems like that to me that all disagree
and are fighting with each other at all times.
I don't know how it's like I'm part of this community.
I just have my own flag for them, you know?
Okay, but there's, and I didn't see this.
So I'm just going by what people are saying,
but apparently he was bad mouthing some,
some other people's kids or something like that.
Well, he said something about, oh, you know, I won't repeat it, but yeah, I kind of shut him down when he said that, so I said, yeah, kids, yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
What else can I do besides say, don't say that, you know?
Do I can I do I just don't know what you're gonna get out of having them on like
Well, yeah, but I'm just saying like what's what's the benefit
I don't know what the benefit is it's not
It's not like you're you you're doing a like everyone knows it's some kind of psychological
Explorative explorative show right? It's kind of like a mishmash of things that happen in the community and that stuff, right?
Well, I mean with you your commute what?
Right exactly
I'm seeing it to bring up like something to bring up someone
controversial and to say well, I just I want to explore their their mentality or their mindset or something like that is
is what, you couldn't have started with someone else?
I've been doing it to a lot of people. I've done it like LD was the same exact same stuff happened with LD
And I've talked to LD many times and we've discussed these things and we talked about
Many other people I've talked about I've interviewed many people in depth about things. I don't know if you
Yeah, I've seen some of the stuff you done. Yeah. Yeah, okay, you have true
This is a serial killer. I mean, it's like there's just a bunch of bodies and stuff like that and violence
if he was that bad he would be in prison because all this video evidence and
everything there wouldn't be like one charge.
It seems to me you're just being defined just to push back on someone telling you what to do
and I do understand that but in this case people are actually kind of right on it.
Right but I still don't care if somebody's in the chat.
Or it's like, when you're in a chat,
on the internet chat, can you reach out and grab somebody?
It's like, has he gone in real life?
I mean, it's like, other than arranging meetings
with streamers and things like that,
is he gonna go, like, jump through the chat?
Is it in danger to anybody, particularly?
No, but he wasn't just in chat, right?
Well, I let him on the panel too,
because I wanted to talk to him.
and understand, and hear maybe, how about someone that's
silenced, they can't get any of their sight, or maybe if they can reveal themselves to be
better or worse than they're portrayed, that it's like
you can't let everybody else have the narrative and not let the person
have a voice too.
Okay, but you didn't even have any background to begin with.
So it's not like you knew the narrative.
Yeah, the less I know the better, the less I know the better, okay?
I knew some information that I could ask you about, but it's like the less I know the better because there's a lot of stuff that is just, I mean, slanderous, and it's like, and some of that was proved, and it's like, I mean, it's just like, there's so many conflicting things to, I mean, it's like, it's just.
I don't know it's like I'm not gonna get to the bottom of it, but okay at the end of the day
Okay, he never did anything against us against my show. What are people?
Okay
So why wouldn't I let somebody that I don't even know okay, let me ask the reaction aside
Are you satisfied with the experiment?
Like, are you satisfied with it,
or do you figure that there's more you need to explore?
Like, are you able to pay?
We can move on.
I would love to explore as much as I can,
talk to all the people I can.
Do I mean with him?
Like, are you gonna have him back to explain more to?
Well, you know, you know, look at SIG, look at SIG. SIG is porn bomb me. SIG has n-word
bomb me. He's come up with a swastika on his head. He said very crazy racial shit. He's,
you know, he showed me his vagina, all these things. And I still let SIG up. I let him
up right now. Look, so I'm pretty much, I'm only letting people up, you know, unless they're
I
Think people are upset because of the this
Sexual nature of the other person's offensive offensive mess you ever seen rally racing
You know what I mean when I say that rally racing, you know what I mean psych it's not just that that he's been you know
He's been creasing in the mall or something like that at least and then it can be can then either admit it or not or
Like I mean, there's really no explanation for it. I mean he could say he was drunk or something
Yeah, that matter
You know what, there's people here that are terrible to me,
that are horrible to me, that are bullying me,
that are cruel.
I keep up bringing my cat, who's like my baby
and stuff like that.
They're always dead, I kidnaps him,
always eating my coyotes, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I abused him, I didn't look at my baby,
he was born under my baby, he said.
And it's like these people,
at least I know what to expect from Brandon, right?
I don't know what to expect from some of these people,
sending shit to my house.
No fucking with my family and stuff like that, right?
And these are people that are celebrating in the community
that everyone is celebrating right now on my show, okay?
So is that right?
No.
I just, I don't know exactly how it applies.
If anyone wants RG, Crystal, or Siegup,
they can go ahead and send me a dollar.
Well, let Crystal or RG, let RG up specifically.
Well, okay, well, if you'd like to donate $10 a little bit.
Come on, man, I, I, no, okay.
I can't, you don't have a super chat.
I can't cash up, I have no, I have many, many other things,
yes, but if you don't want to do it, it's fine.
You don't have to.
No, it's just like, I'm not gonna say I'm not gonna be here bad-mouthed.
I mean, you talk to me, okay, because you can talk rationally at least, but I'm not gonna be like,
Like I'm you're looking at people are looking at me putting a dollar amount on it
I mean, it's like it's like for the fucking grief it gets me
I'm not gonna do me any good. I mean, I'm yelling me or like I've already heard of it
I know what they're gonna say. I've heard it before I okay. I apologize
You know she's saying the most horrible shit about me
My daughter like he's calling me like, you know, it's thing. I'm endorsing the behavior when I don't know what I would like
at least let them talk and yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You did not have those fucking forehead lines. I just look at you look at a fucking 80 year old look
Go ahead laugh again. Let me see those forehead lines. That's intense. He wouldn't doing you bro
He will be doing to you. He will beat us doing to you loser. That bitch is sucking your fucking energy. Look at those. Oh my god
Those lines bro, I don't even have one of those not even one
Brother when I see one of those coming. I'm gonna you know, that's a problem. You guys what is it? Okay?
With wrinkly lines, okay, that's intense, bro
Talk to me who gave you those lines
That's worry. That's that's stress brother. You sit in that gaming chair
On panels 24 hours when you don't you can we talk about that? Can we sleep a shut the fuck up?
You sleep you're in your mom's house in Canada
Literally in your mom's condo taking care of your uncle with dementia. You have no hair
You you're you look twice your age and you're up here talking shit. What's your deal, man?
What's your end game? You think that little smirk does something you little bald ugly fuck
We a little smirk you just smirk
Yo, bro, it's the funniest thing. I love watching you honestly when you're on beaters
I tune in every time and I just examine your facial expressions and I'm like look at this loser
I can read every thought in your mind with your facial expression
Aren't you depressed a week ago and you're crying you were crying to me a week ago. You were crying. Oh
I'm depressed. Oh my mind. I'm gonna kill myself. I'm depressed. I never said that
I've always said I came into save your life and so I told you don't give up get on that horse
Do that shit. You're a depressed loser. You're a depressed loser. Honestly, at this point,
you should just do it. You know what I'm saying? Just go for it, bro. Okay. Go to the nearest bridge
and do a swan dive right off that shit. All right. Do life a favor. Do humanity a favor.
Because what are you doing up here? What favor are you doing to humanity besides nothing?
Bombita with sweepy. Oh, look at his little eyebrows shake your head move your little eyes
Look at him. Look at her left. Look to the right. Look at him. He's laughing
I'm fucking murdering this motherfucker right now. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I love it. Yeah, you know it
And yo NorCal is AMC by the way psyche
We got the info nor cow that little faggot on beat us panel go nor cow is
allied master computer and the story I don't want you shit I rug and and I want
nobody talking shit we got you tonight nor cow or should I say Tony the cement
loser go ahead send more cement said send more cement haha send more cement
Fuckin loser
Oh, so man pizza
You fucking losers tried and failed so hard. It was scary. You're pathetic. All of you. No, Cal's pathetic
I like master computers pathetic your whole community is pathetic
But that is criticism at all the retard shut the fuck up
Shut up. Oh boy. I can't hear you. Would you say?
This thing talking
No, I don't
I really I
What's wrong with your mouth and like your cheeks? What little blinds? They've got lines everywhere. That's so weird, bro
So you're okay with the way things are going
Tiki lines look at
With these wrinkly lines look at psyche's forehead not one line at all
Beautiful a beautiful forehead Jesus Christ. You just got blown out of the water Alex and you don't even realize it. Holy fuck
So that's it like you know, you don't want to discuss it at all anymore
Go ahead. I
Can't hear what you're saying raise your mic loser
Look at his dick. He's delusional
Blowing out of the water for no reason who blew me out of the water. Why went and where and how drink a little cup
Oh, stand up and show us your tits you fat fuck you got man tits down to your fucking ankles
You you look skinny, but you got tits there. So I know your weird body. I saw it
You stood up once and I saw your tits bro and the story
It's okay cuz thank you's probably gonna erase this channel
Because of this. You know, he's a pussy. He doesn't keep channels up anymore, but it's okay
There's 9,000 people watching and listening
You know some people are gonna get
Bro go suck a dick an idiot sucked dick and the story. How about that?
Just saying man. Just saying to go suck a dick
No, I know show those little shoulders to yours. That's his maneuver. He shrugs his shoulders
That's my favorite that when he shrugs his little shoulders like a bitch
Yo, that's all he does. He shrugs his shoulders
That's his maneuver, bro
Little shoulder shrug and freak. Where's your little dog? I can't hear what you're saying
Oh, yeah, I'm saying there's a sport called bridge jumping and you wear a harness and so it's what Christine told me all about it
What?
Oh my god
Sorry
Do you ever get out of that chair, bro? That chair must smell like shit
Your ass every day like enough, bro. That's crazy
You know, there's actually a sport called bridge jumping and you use a harness that Christine told me about it and so
Look at thing that is he can't even hear he's like which year which year worst thing that is this guy's like trying to listen in
He's deaf dumb and blind already all deaf dumb blind and crippled at 58 years old my peeps
68 it's a 68 or 58, bro
58 I try to help you as so you know what my help so fuck you each getting died loser
All right, so we're done talking about it
By a television see you tomorrow sign or a boom we aren't adios
I mean my Ronys man. I want them all to myself. You understand? I'm a jealous motherfucker. I want Ronys
That's my man. The fuck out of you thing that is
It's my man. The fuck I'll break his hands, bro. Don't touch my man. The fucking voice even doing here Ronys
No, fuck don't know everyone's like tell me they're opinion about you, but I'm really like not my
It's like wow
It's kind of shocked like that people can't even be in a chat room nowadays. I understand like the
I just I don't know all those things that sometimes I mean to have a kind of good friend talk to me about it
And it's like but she's still I was still willing to hear the guy out
Oh
Jesus in the back crying, so I got a job so these people can come up because they can handle me
She's not back stage here. He left
Rizzer my man Rizza
Oh, yeah, I review or exactly sign all right yours has to la vista. I'll have your
See you next week. There's a woman named Simone and she was the adventure and she was
Now he's gonna drop I think you think he
Hey, thank you
Yeah
I mean, as long as it's like
Broke the case acts notice no cow was um AMC and I was like I knew it acts was to lead detective on the case
Well, I just know that he was I have a tweaker and stuff so
You know, and oh, you know
When you it's a most disgusting thing I've looked I've known the most disgusting people in the world
But you know what the way he eats french fries is
Oh my
Yeah, and the devil probably
You heard it exactly like I hate just the way he eats
He's a man, but you heard what he said also like I learned my lesson like he learned
He cannot take you down that motherfucker learned the hard way
Like I gave up. He basically gave up.
North cow AMC gave up like I tried for a year and a half.
You're not going to keep sending manure forever.
OK, he lost that shit.
Yeah, I mean, it's like to go suck a dick and hang out with fucking beta
and talk about concerts back in the day.
I'm from San Francisco.
Fucking loser.
Told you stop fucking with us you fuck
Choo-choo
Yeah, he learned bro
Choo-choo, there you go
I
Crystal Marie do me a favor get you hot hot ass up here, baby. Let me hear that
Crystal Marie's voice is um, she says I'm bullshit to me. She said recently really bad
But she's uh, she said tell me is messing with me because I did that
Tony the the same loser we're talking about
It's not messing with crystal Marie. That's bullshit. She's in on April
That's bullshit. She's in on it. She's fucking with you and now that Tony's losing his little grip on you
They're coming in hot trying to mindfuck you like Tony Tony. That means crystal Marie was in on that bullshit
Brother, it's a team network. You think it was just Tony. It was all of them when that shit happens things like that
It's a collective team of people doing it to make that shit happen
Christine Tony
Bronsburg Exile
Beta they work together on that shit
Just like the all-range coming the other night
and they come on the panel and ruin my show.
You think that's a coincidence?
Exactly, bro.
It doesn't take brain surgery to figure it out.
That's not a coincidence.
That's a team.
And I heard many a times them come out of their face like,
oh, yeah, but what happens when we send a pallet of shit
to your house?
Like, who would say that unless you're on that team?
I know because everyone's saying yay Tony like they're all like hey to yo Tony's North cow. He came on beat us tonight
was talking shit like a loser and he admitted twice that he's done with this shit
He's no longer gonna bother you. He learned and he even said it
I learned the hard way and you know what he said the guy actually learned bro
He said the less time every hour I spend up here bothering you people
I can do something with my life productive like the man actually woke up and got it
He woke up and got it bro
Like you think you're gonna run McQueen and psyche off like we'll die
We'll go to the fucking grave bro bring it that guy's an old loser trying to fuck with you
And he learned he he called your bluff basically and you won
So here. Oh, he's done. You're never gonna get no nothing ever again. He's out of the picture, pal
No, I'm not a picture
It's no count it's me
It's crystal Marie. Hey, baby
You better not be in on a crystal, please. I'm definitely not in on no shit
But I'll tell you that fucking psyche is in on some weird shit
Take one
I'm some weird shit because he's hanging out with this fucking weirdo that everybody he knows that guy is a fucking creep everybody knows
That guy's a creep that guy's been a creep. He's been a creep you think that's like
Only guy that's banned Brandon Q
The only motherfucker that is a complete
You know somebody that we don't you know a PDF file for real life that we could actually count
For because he says he has a 12 year old girlfriend. He says that he did this and that he says he is this
He did this we seen him break it try to break into an old lady's house
We seen him do the nastiest fucking outrageous like the most disgusting things that nobody needs to fucking be a part of
You can't I'm saying you're good. Don't are you okay? No, I'm not because I think that guy is sick
So you don't hang out with him. He's not in your life
Yesterday for a little bit fighting Q and you know bullshit, but it's not the end of the world
Or hey, please don't talk to that guy. I
The guy is so
Crystal I don't like people you know he tried to
Beacon Patriot he tried to rape her on camera
I don't I'm not gonna take your word for that. You need to show me
Everything I'm saying is on camera
Okay
That wasn't rape. I saw the video psyche showed it the girl went to bed and he like tickled her or something
Did he showed them when he laid on top of her and put his fucking
Obviously she liked the guy like
Why did you take it to the award? No, this woman has pots. She's a drug addict. She's not a normal woman
Who VP goes there? Who would go to fucking Brandon Q's house and choose in a bad situation?
Who would ever go to that motherfuckers house?
Look at your socks. You're walking around in socks. I see the toes
Look at the toes
I don't care about Brandon Q. I want to see them toes, baby
I mean let it out
Banned. Banned. Branding Q.
That's I've been here in the ship for two days
Branding cube and a cube. What the fuck at least the kid came up and protected himself if he was not guilty
He was just right away
He is a registered has to be he has to be
There's no other way around it unless like where he lives. I can say they they really don't I don't know
He lives by the border
You know, he gets away with a lot of
A couple of people
Hold on what do you mean by Arizona? He was in Arizona border. He lives right there on the border and he like
So he lives by the border and
He you fucking bullies mother fuckers
Are you pregnant did I just see a giant belly?
Hey
It's not big, right, you know
You still have eggs flopping around there. You better get some kids going baby. Come on
Don't pull into you know menopause land and you know come on
Let's go
You're hot. I don't understand the problem. You see my butt. I think you see my butt
I don't see your butt. I see your toes and I thought I saw a ponzo
But seriously, you're not
I do not have a pond you have a pond. Oh my god. Look how hot she is
But don't do that. Don't do that. Seriously. That's not my goal here. Don't you only do that for me
I don't want everybody seeing your ponzo. Okay
I don't have one
Well, that ponson needs to be filled with a little mini you like way way
Okay, that's the reason
We're not talking it like we're talking about what's going on right now. I'm talking about the situation
this guy's
and fucking psyche and
LD I want to talk with the ponson
I'm missing what do you want to talk about? What do you want to talk about?
I'm just saying that everybody should watch their motherfucking backs with that fucking dude
What dude Brandon Q. I never heard of him till yesterday never met the guy in my life
I came up. He was there with Q. I was throwing my two cents in you know, I don't know
Well, I just don't like psyche being so chummy with them because he's really a pedophile me
Psychies trying to be neutral though. No, no, no stock. He's in love
No, he's not oh
Yes, he is in love. That's my man. Who's he in love with no easy to you are done dude
He's done with you
What he's cheating on me with fucking completely done with you. He's he's already moved on with Brandon Q
Is that what he is right now because I don't know he is right now. Is he with Brandon Q right now?
psyche you little hussy get your ass up here
Where the fuck is Roni's ass cheeks, buddy. Where the fuck you been man? You've been with you
We're not on you. Let me know. No, let me smell. I gotta take a whiff if I smell Brandon Q's perfume on you my man
It's not gonna
You smell
You smell like McDonald's you smell like cigars
No, Q no Q
And
No, because fucking crystal Marie said you were fucking Brandon Q in the yard
Right now
That's what you said
I do like Latinos, but actually I do like this guy named God body that's been on the show
that guy will bond you to the floor bro that's too much wait you definitely got to ride him
he can't be on top he'll die that's much that's like that um that other
I saw him actually you were like fucking sub to this guy and I looked at it I'm like
what's up to this monster like what the hell it's like Lu for Rig no I'm like what are you
That's what I like, that's what I like.
He's really nice.
That's what you like, in a way.
I like him and you like, but he can't be.
Okay, so Alex, I told this to guys,
I said, I'm really easy to manipulate my hot guy,
like a hot enough guy can like give me to rob a bank.
And then he said, then he commented on the vote.
I made a short of that.
He commented on it and he's like,
hey, let's, hey, let's go rob a bank.
A hot guy can make you rob a bank like hey, bro, and you fall in love with them
And it'll be like go rob that fucking city bank across the street. You'll be like, okay. It's that what you just said
I can make you rob a bank
That's the funniest shit I've ever heard dick and didn't you make it shorter that I could have sworn I saw a shorter that
That's funny
Because it's true. No, it's fucking true a
Year ago, I could have made you rob a bank. You were in love with me. I've been like Ronis go fucking
Hit that old chase bank
Honey
Who do you love though? Who is your who is your target? Who do you love? Oh?
I mean, not most people that come to most people that are I know in the show. I would not
Untrackable. No, there's gotta be someone that you just dying for you dream like I wish
Joker I know
Joker Joker
Play play now you gotta play broke like mountain
Yeah, Joker what a stupid question like how retarded am I? I
you don't know what they've done, man, so
Joke, where are you, bro?
Come back to papa.
Now he's Mr. Extendo. He calls himself Mr. Extendo.
I wish I could get rid of you. What do you say?
I wish I could forget you.
I wish I could quit you, yeah?
Oh, I guess I could. I don't know.
I love this ghost, I think.
I think he might get you banned, I don't know.
I don't know. You can't show, like, maybe a commercial or something.
a commercial. Or could you? Commercials. What do you think of these flowers I made? You made the flowers? Wow. They're so beautiful. You're amazing. She's so talented and hot and just amazing. She's the perfect woman.
Yeah, I got some more stuff. I'm gonna make some more, actually. I have this. Crystal Stewart.
Can you see?
They were not what is that? What are we looking at? What the hell is that? What do you mean?
Okay, it's right here
Okay, I have something here. I have like that stuff. I have to
And then you like these sticks and then a hot glue gun and then you just shape it and then you know, it's very simple
Why am I on here alone because you were we were showing your projects we were supposed to show what you mean that's why now you're flooring your socks we want to see what you mean no these are well the you can't tell because they're
And then you take the sticks, right?
You take these little tiny sticks
and then you see these little tiny sticks right here.
And then you make a little cut out, right?
And then you hot glue the gun,
these sticks into a little thing
and then you, you know, crooked them.
And then you string it together
and then you put it into a swirly pole.
That's probably what these things, these things are super easy, uh, as well.
Do you sell them or you make them for like a hobby?
Well, I do.
Well, see, listen, I did, in a sense, because, okay, I will be, because, uh, Heidi was selling
And then I have a storefront area, so I could and I was like, oh shit, I could I could sell these for 60 and make them for looking in 30.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll set up.
Beautiful.
I want to buy one.
A hundred dollars for a
Oh, it's $1.25 for three
Water flying?
Isn't that crazy at the store?
But no, I sell mine for 60.
Oh, never mind. It's not mine.
I'm not selling mine.
Okay, because they're not my store.
I'm making them. Yeah, they're mine.
Roni, do we have to go visit her, man?
We have to.
I don't know what she wants to meet me.
Do you want to meet our psyche, Crystal?
and Alex
I mean if we don't listen right you got a gas room obviously it looks like a you have a house
Is there a second bedroom where we can crash?
I have three bedrooms, but see the thing is
No, they're all closets, and then I have a computer room. I have a computer room that
Be like our camera
I
Imagine you me and Roni, but I really need to get into that because I really you know like mom was saying like I
got like
Hundreds of pairs of jeans that I never even wear hundreds. I'm talking maybe even thousands
That were like
And I like when you wear the big jeans like like looks like it's for five people, but you're all thin and it's like hot like
With baggy clothes
You know why I wore baggy clothes is because
And I always kind of war by
And the one men's
Slavering over you and in mind fucking you. I hope that's good. I didn't want I didn't want everybody like
completely like exactly and then every time i went to the like because i would never mind i i
don't want to get that's why rain has to correct with the sheets over the women and the eyeball cut
outs because don't look at my girl exactly so christin marie you think i want you going to
supermarket in fucking spandex and a short top so every man on earth can just mindfuck you like
Okay, and girls know that too. It's fucked up. Yeah
But I don't think that for yourself and your relationship and your man, and you know
That are by comfort ability and like people are like thinking that like made the beach. Yeah, she's shooting city, but
I'm saying
I just know what I'm saying.
You know, sometimes you don't, it's not called for, and it's like fucking.
And clothing has parted to do with that.
It doesn't matter. I'm saying it doesn't fucking matter.
If you go to the supermarket with a camo toe in a bra on,
obviously everyone's mind fucking you.
If you go up to the supermarket with jeans and a nice little holter top
and like a normal human.
hey yeah you're a beautiful girl but we're not like nobody's gonna show their like
don't mind fucking you trust me but it's gets worse when you're the fucking like half naked and
showing shit i ran as a ride with that
the only thing they got right is that shit
But she'd over the head bullshit. I kind of agree with that. I mean honestly, I kind of don't
I mean other than like like going to the pool and like like concerts and stuff and like actual shows that I've been in I
You know, and maybe that's a little bit and it is a little bit weird because I have to train myself
You didn't buy a car or whatever it's called
But you don't even respect your women. That's why they hate the West like you Americans
You don't even respect your women. You let them go out and she shrinks and fucking like, you know
They hate that shit. These people put sheets over there women like don't look at my girl
opposite. That's insane like most people, I would never go out and like some I don't think most women would, but some people would maybe for fun.
Uh, but there is different kinds of people, you know, like, you know, we aren't judging, right? Are we judge? Can we judge whores?
Because whores wear clothes like that.
Like as far as like, you know
Or is that a judging
Or is it are we judging there is there is okay, there is a difference though
There's a difference between like somebody dressing
uh a sexy or productive or then
From somebody that's dressing like a whore or you know, that's trying to just like just wearing a bra and underwear
You know like you see these horse go out and fucking bra dude, it's like oh my god
Don't really see women in bras like walking around
Trash it does all the time
Shrash is staying with her kid. She takes her kid out in a brawl
You know, you didn't you don't see that
Didn't see them
Yeah, her last stream where she got drunk and drove with her kid fucking
Oh, yeah, she drove, um, almost, I don't want to know, I'm not interested, over an hour or 45 minutes or something drunk as fuck with her kid.
So, I mean, are people allowed to get drunk, like the kids? Are you just driving or something?
Yeah, she was drinking and driving from Trump to Vegas, back to Vegas to Trump.
Parampa? What is the verse of that?
Parampa is where she lives the one town that it's legal to have it's legal to for sexual stuff
She lives in the one town that's legal in America for sex
It's a very small town it's a very small town that Trashah lives in
Well, but it's the only town in America that you can sell sex in
I can't hear you your volume. Don't bring up don't talk about her. She's not here. Oh
Okay, well, okay keep that same fucking energy buddy. Okay. I would
So somebody brings me up you better never fucking bring me up again. Let's make sure that
Well, not that they're slandering you, so that's what I mean, if they're slandering you, then I would not let you slander you.
Well, your volume is retarded, so it's kind of pointless.
Hey, Joni, how are you? 80 in the room full of likes. I know I know it's kind of sad now. It's like
Johnny it's okay. We're used to it. Don't worry
Lose it. Lose it. It's like likes it. I mean come on, Joni. Hey, what do you have to say?
Like I mean you can't do it so who gives a fuck hit the like
If you want to
It's only talk, you know, and that's why you only fucking try to disrespect me
You know what? Hey Alex
Do you know that this guy fucking tries to use fucking Kim's picture as me sometimes to try to fucking
Blame me as a fucking retard
You do psyche and guess what you're getting a time three times ten times fucking 20
Okay, guess what I am the ultimate
I mean, I just can't. Yeah, in your phone. No, I don't know that. That's a lot. That's a complete lie. He kids. What do you what the fuck you talking about?
I never said nothing about kids, dude. You're the first time to use the kids. Am I retarded? I can hear. I never said nothing. I said pictures of me.
Oh, is that what she said? Sorry. I could have sworn on her
Okay, that's Kim. Yeah as Joe's girlfriend Kim. Yeah, he did it for
He did it for trash. Hey, guess what psyche you're gonna get ten times that buddy
You're gonna get ten times for trying to use me for trash a fucking value fucking faggot
Wonder what you push the case like we try to fucking dog me for trash of one night. Yeah, buddy
You're gonna get it bud. You're gonna get it
Two seconds ago, she was showing us her stupid birds that she makes on Etsy now she's threatening you
What's wrong with this bipolar bitch?
I have no birds
You're bipolar, you know
You're bipolar bitch. You were just
Fucking sicko you retarded your mind is out of
Your mind is out of it. You're fucking weird. Oh, you think I'm somebody else too
To your mind right crystal Marie your crystal Marie. Who do I think you are?
Okay, so you think I have an Etsy and I'm selling birds you fucking weirdo
Get it together. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you're a retard exactly
You just said you're selling your flower we can't even sell we can't even hear anything cannot hear him thing that is sorry you psych
I can't hear anything the birds are from my place
Yeah, remember mine thing that is I'm so sorry that we got into it last time up here, okay?
You know
Yeah, it's okay, and I said some pretty rude things last time
We were together when I was drunk and all that shit and angry and all that shit, so I apologize
That's okay. Uh, you know, it's but the same back at you, you know
Now one block me in chat damn it
Who's blocked in chat you are yeah by crystal
I am black people man, there's a lot of mud, is she?
I just asked Chris to talk to me.
There's a Tony Bennett in the chat.
Are you a mud, Chris?
I'm not a mud dude.
Yeah
For good reason baby you're out of your mind you sell birds on that see you talk shit you love us now you hate psyche
It's for a good reason that you're not a model. Okay?
Give me kisses give me kisses crystal
Give me come on. Give me tongue
Who's got the stupid bird in the background
Me Jesus Christ close the window bro. That's a nightmare
Being that is the selling birds on it see now
It's called
Can you hear that guy I can tell that he's talking so he's not muted, but I can't tell what he's saying
Um
Oh my your birds though, they're very chirpy, you know white birds they're you know nature's birds
They are your birds
I own my birds. I swear I own my birds. I have a white squirrel. I have
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I
love the birds I have all kinds of birds but I'm saying all the other animals
bring the birds yeah yeah all the wildlife they bring the birds
Yeah, if it wasn't for the other wildlife the birds wouldn't be around well
I suppose yeah, it's like the insects and the and the smaller animals in worms and stuff. I
Feel like well cuz I feed them
Okay, I feed the birds
Right and squirrels
I'm a white squirrel
I don't know where I think he comes from Washington
State or DC I'm from Missouri. Okay. I believe he comes from Washington. I don't know
I don't know where white squirrels. I believe they come from Washington
DC I guess you mean I guess I don't know I mean I guess cuz it's the only white squirrel I like out videos
Have a one white squirrel, and you have albino. He's an albino, and you said some chipmunks or something like that
Beavers beavers. Yes. I don't think all my girls exist. Oh, well, they're woodchucks
What you do for woodchuck wood
No, she has two woodchucks that she named Jason Bieber. She doesn't have beaver
See, he's right. He's right. There were chucks that I named Justin Bieber. He really beaver
She doesn't have beaver. She's got two woodchucks that are named after the beavers
Yes, I can't baby. I don't miss a beat. Okay?
Alex is the crystal whisperer. Oh, I know he is he got it. I
Love Alex Alex you're great. And so are you saying you guys are both good guys. Oh, thank you
Alex I mean I'm freaking even though
Not an albino beaver. I just shut up. Give me kisses, baby
And albino squirrel. Okay, I have an albino squirrel, but I have two woodchucks
That I call
Beavers Justin Ailey Beaver. I don't know. I don't know where it went. I thought they were beavers
Neither of the beavers are beavers
No, I thought they were beavers. Okay, and I had a beavers or beavers
None of the beavers are beavers. Yeah
Not not beavers, but they're beavers
Like you guys are I don't
Are they beavers or beavers?
I hear Paige, she's coming home, Paige, she's cool, she was here, who is Paige?
Paige, I'm gonna burn some fucking Seiji for Paige, I'm not kidding, I'm gonna burn some
Let's see if I can do this
Are you actually gonna play with fire right now?
Why not that's awesome
All right, speaking of beavers. How's your beaver? Is it stuffed? Is it a hairy beaver?
And I'm talking the thing that is Chris, I'm talking to you
that
That means she had a date bro. They don't get the nails done for no reason. She's looking for man love
Crystal was that a tobacco pack in the bag
What do you have tobacco patches for
Recovery patch drink smarter
Recovery from what
There's pagey
Come on, baby commando business
Pajie come back. I don't know. He muted me. I don't know
She's jealous. Um
Pages jealous crystal. Thank you. You're here
No, we can hear you
Paging you're not as a good sage. You're as crystal Marie. That's sage my friend. Did you just crystal hit it?
She'll page how it's done more fire man. Are those tootsie rolls in the back there? What were those?
Crystal marino, so tell me the candy jars right now. You know, you know
Undered a one-year-old lady made this for me. It looks like it
Look how cute it is. Oh, yeah
That's sweet. That's nice. I know 101. Okay. Now show me the candy jars. Were those tootsie rolls?
Yes, tootsie rolls. Awesome. Awesome.
What was the recovery patch for? I'm sorry, you were muted. It's for drinking.
How many do they have to get to the middle of a tootsie roll?
I think it's five, honestly, five licks.
Five licks?
Look at the middle.
It's for drink.
It's drink smarter.
It's it's vitamin.
Remember that commercial?
There was a little owl with the 20 roll.
How many licks?
Yeah, I remember.
He would bite it at the end.
Remember that shit?
So like what does that mean like to help you cut down on drinking or just no
It makes you burp. It just makes you it just makes you recover faster
I don't know for me it makes me burp because I don't ever burp unless I don't know
Was that a sample or something or do you buy those?
They come in four packs
Man, how many did it
Yeah, it's it's a one zippy right the one path, right?
Okay
Comes in it comes in four
And it's a patch like you actually just you put it on your arm or your chest. I mean
Yeah, put on your arm, right I
Have it on my belly because I have oh you definitely had a date with those nails
Crystal Marie tell us who's the guy?
I have cramps and so I put it on there just in case or
No, but your nails your nails show or paint a different picture
No one gets the nails that hot done unless they have a date
Yeah, those candies were awesome. I want I want a tootsie roll
Yeah, you know, I had this weird obsession. I love candy, but um, I try not to eat it as much as I do. Um,
I had this obsession when I was younger with
Chinese candy because we used to travel a lot. We had show cars
so we used to go all around the country and show cars around and
I would get go to all these different Chinese restaurants and getting all these different kinds of fucking
Different kind of lollipops and then my brother's friend
Yeah, oh
I've got
I've got a lot of I got 11 brothers. Okay, but one of my brothers, you know, I've got bad-ass brothers, but
But one of them the you know him and his buddy
I had all this collection, right of all these Chinese fucking suckers and shit
And yeah, they went in and fucking a all my shit, dude
It was so but you know what I did is like I ripped the car up the emblem off their cars when I was really young
You went into Chinese, you went into Chinese, you went into Chinese, you went into Chinese,
you went into Chinese, you went into Chinese, you went into Chinese, you went into Chinese,
That's what it all means to me.
I took all of them, like, what, like, the homie of, like, my brother's friend?
Oh, dude, I took every, like, you only want to know.
I got in so much trouble for that, but they stole my candy.
And that she was a collector from all over the country and all over the world and shit.
And they didn't get no trouble for that shit.
That's it. That's the Chinese for you, man. That's that's what happens.
Fucking Chinese. OK, now let's get back to those tootsie.
So. Did you buy those at a Chinese store?
I mean, I was. Of course, there were restaurants and like.
When we would go to car shows on your kids, I would collect candy
OK, from like different shapes of suckers and like.
Oh, like the coolest shit like so cool gummies. I had like a huge game. Yeah, oh
But that doesn't look like me
But
Okay, but it wasn't 11 brother these places
Guys come and kill you bro, and I have one sister I have one sister
Five brothers
Page you're the oldest so they're all younger is that what she's saying I
Have one little brother
And everyone else is older than you mm-hmm, and he's by a different mother
I have a younger brother and sister the brother is from a different father
Yeah, yeah, I'm jealous. I'm an only child
Yeah
That's all different age we are you know, I'm in my 40s and he's in his 20s
That's why I hate when I hear like people like I don't get along with my brother or sister like man
I wish I had one like that. That's just crazy. Yeah, my my brother
When he was born like I'm not a planet a total generation apart my brother and I no
Like this is ridiculous the fucking
the reason they say this is because I
Okay
One day me and fucking or cow are talking about school like back in the day like back in the day shit
and I
Was telling him about when I was a kid, you know, I took aviation one just to get out of school
You know what I mean? Just to get out of class, you know, just to get out of that school because it was
Off-school campus, you know what I mean?
And then it became a whole big deal, but that was in high school. They were talking about I took aviation one in high school
Now I'm a pilot
See this is these are how these people think I still think it's awesome that that a high school even offers aviation courses at all
Like even if it's yeah, that's what I was saying. That's what I was saying
I was like when I was talking to NorCal we were talking about
You know, he was saying that his school did but not a lot of other schools did and it was just the timing
your classes cost a lot you need like 500 just
Every time or like a thousand just to go up in the air like that
Money to do that. I looked into
Getting my pilot's license when I was younger. Yeah, it's not just I want to be a pilot. You better have money
At the time when I was like in my
But it doesn't it depends on what part of the country you live in because this is like it's studied here in my area
But it was at least 30 grand to go through all the all the schools to get your up to a commercial license and then to actually start with some of the smaller commercial airlines.
It was like 30 grand to qualify to get there.
Well, yeah, it's what I wanted to do that, man. That's totally I wanted to be a pilot.
I don't know exactly how much.
That's why let's like stop or like drop out because they just can't afford I don't know
I wouldn't say because see it really because see in our area like sometimes
For instance, there's a lot of
Jobs that can qualify you to be in there so
You could they could pay you to you know to be qualified. Yeah, you know what I mean
I mean your private license Alex for just a like a regular Cessna type thing like a 182 whatever
Does not cost 30 gram that that's only a few grand for that. Yeah, that's
Like it's not even that. Yeah, yeah, not even that. Yeah, I'm talking like 500 bucks
Yeah, like maybe you have to qualify for like double for
Multiple engines then then you go to commercial you have to qualify for jets and you know, and yeah, that's true
Yeah, it depends on where you're going with
In the classes and he quit in the middle. He's like I can't afford it, bro
Every time I go up it's like 500 thousand dollars
and he became a stewardess he was going to become a pilot
oh yeah and then he just couldn't do it and you know he still was in the airline
industry and became a stewardess but yeah takes a lot of money to do
it's daunting yeah you need to you need to have some support to be able to do it
like it's tough to just do it if you know on your own if you're like middle
class lower class especially and we're middle class but I will say that
I lived on it. Oh, well, I don't know. I'm not gonna even talk about it. So it's like NASCAR racing
You ever looked at NASCAR?
I lived on a popular line. That's like a million
You're not becoming a NASCAR racer unless you have like 10 million under your belt. Oh my gosh
It takes a lot of money. I know so many just to try to become one. But see, you know how easy that is in America
It's like in Missouri
You know
Do you know I'm saying though you can't become a little kid and say I want to be formerly one racer
Unless you come from a prominent family with
They have you and you a chance to become a former boy
Well, where I was grabbing they have junk cars for 50 bucks that you could fucking rent you pay
250 you can fucking rent a fucking junk car for 50 bucks to fucking
just crash the motherfucker you can shoot it you can kill it you can do anything after it
after you fucking race the motherfucker but it's got an engine like a motherfucker all you're paying
for is for that $250 for that one little spin you're talking like american like like stock car
racing and shit where it just starts like in the fields like you know in somebody's field and all
But when he's talking for Formula One, that's shit from a very, very young age.
I'm telling you, that's where, okay.
Well, I'm telling you, that's...
It was one, and then NASCAR...
From a very young age.
That's why he's saying you need to have money.
Oh my gosh.
That's why he's saying you need to have money, because you're paying for all these things,
like from a very, very young age.
It's not like you're just hanging with your friends,
building cars, and wasting them in backyard.
No, we're not. You can just take shit.
You can just fix it up.
You know what I'm saying?
You don't want to stuff like that.
It's a whole pedigree with them, man.
These guys are not like us,
where we can just build like a go cart in the backyard.
I know, I know, but that's not what they do.
You can build something in your backyard
that makes it like fucking better
than the fucking anywhere you could ever imagine.
I know.
Hmm
But yeah, my dad and my brother are mechanics and my brother is a fucking badass fucking
I'm not even getting yeah, but he's a badass at that shit and
he's badass at like
Well, it's really a motor car motocross and all the fucking all that shit. Yeah
In stock cars in American stock cars like NASCAR. That's generally how it started, right?
It's people just building their own cars and racing them locally in like, yeah, locally organized shit, right?
Mm-hmm
Yeah, they do you want to be a woman or a NASCAR racer you would have a lot of money to get to there
Just like college you got to pay a tuition
But more money
I would have million be a formula driver formula one. Oh my god. Those guys are
but you didn't have millions of dollars
dude, I had a buddy that was 18 years old, professional
he drove, he fucking set up his sister's car dude
look up what it takes to be a Formula 1 driver
you need a million
who fucked up his sister fucking
why would you even want to be a Formula 1 driver if you already had millions
and made it a fucking monster car, okay?
It's just the point that the system has set up fucked up in the game. Okay, no little kid in the project
It's gonna be a formula one driver no matter what he does
You know the reflexes those guys have the formula one drivers like the really the high-speed drivers
You know the reflexes those guys have
It's it's amazing
Oh my gosh, you should have seen this guy, dude. My friend Nick, 112 miles an hour with his knee, with his knee, driving 112 miles an hour with his fucking knee.
Try 212, baby.
Going in and out of traffic, professional driver. He was an after driver, but I would say we did NASCAR without NASCAR.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Yeah, I love speed like I really do
Like that that sensation the the acceleration being pushed back in your seat fucking love it
He did that to try to scare me he was doing that because he wanted to scare me who what oh
At that moment
Yeah, I love
Not only do those guys have incredible going in a fucking he was in a fucking off
It was off-street. It was it was not street legal fucking car, you know
Okay, listen not only like formula one drivers and I kind of shit not only do they have amazing reflexes because everything's coming at them at
Like 200 miles an hour, right? So you got to be really quick seeing the shit way up there
But the lateral forces they're pulling like five six G's like left and right when they're making turns in that
I like that's that's tough. That's physically
That's that's hard on you man. Do that. I will tell you one thing
yeah, I will tell you my friend Nick was like a professional driver and
He was really
Really really good. He's really good
and he had a really bad neck problems, I will say.
You know, like stiffness in his neck.
Yeah.
I, you know, from driving like that, like always like so fast.
He couldn't drive anywhere slow.
I'm I used to be the same when I was younger. Absolutely. Everything was like a race. I always had to be passing somebody
It's like a mentality
I've definitely calmed down, but I had a lot of speeding tickets when I was younger. I had my license suspended
Just once for too many points because of speeding. Oh
Man, I had a suspended another time too for careless driving, but that was that was dumb
Well
I'm doing that
But I've really come down like last 20 years whatever I've been fine. I haven't had a ticket in like yeah at least 20 years
Hey midnight, yeah, I'm pretty cautious and I would drink and drive. Oh, I've never done that
I think that's but the worst I did was blow a yellow up here. It's like when you're just under
I think you have to be like five five percent or something like that under
And you get a warning and you look faster. Don't do it, man
The wall you can't drive for it's not working if you get a warning. No, it's not dude
It's not worth putting somebody else in risk like you're risking
Just walk you fucked up
Yeah
You know the worst I ever think there's a lot of other options I
Know I agree and that's scared the shit and me just the warning itself. It's just like oh my god
I really I honestly thought I was fine
And okay, no more chances
Yeah, bro, long thoughts before I forget and I'm up here
Um, I just want you guys to know that I do not support
Fucking psyche being around fucking nasty brain and Q
I fucking hate that dude, that guy is a predator.
He is a disgusting person.
He is a danger to everyone around like that he talks to.
And nobody should be put in danger.
Or even like that guy is like completely like insane.
Yeah, I don't, I think everybody else is in agreement with you.
I'm not Crystal land. I'm sorry. Why do I keep doing that? I wish she didn't come around because now it that mean just keeps
because crystal and just recently came
oh my gosh
and I
I love you so much
like if you're doing so good
I have no
issues or whatever I mean
and then I
I do not fuck with that other crystal
like crystal is fucking retarded dude
she's like a
she's a scripter
she only does scripted drama
but she doesn't like christian
she doesn't like christian crystal
so you should team up with her
Lots of people are retarded. That's that's the that's the thing around here. That's something that I don't realize I don't do scripted drama
But but still lots of people are retarded whether it's scripted or not. Oh
Yeah, that's for sure. I mean
That's what I'm saying. I've come to realize there are a lot of retarded people around here
I mean, I try not to I mean literally like
Uh, the time is that I go crazy is that motherfuckers push me there, you know, it's like it's you know how it is
It's like non-going. It's like fucking it's just like poke poke poke poke poke poke poke poke poke poke
You're just poking in my fucking face and expecting me not to fucking snap
You know, I hear you I know so when it starts getting you know
Is is see that's the thing is is to actually recognize when it's getting to a point where you do need to step away
If only for just a couple days, right? Just to kind of like
Let this shit like roll off my back a bit, you know before I start reacting to everything
Yeah
That's the eyes and when to do that that's what I'm saying. I'm not saying that I'm good at that. I'm saying that is the hard part
Yeah, that is the hard part. No, it's really not the hard part because it's never gonna go away
They're gonna keep bringing it up every time you come over
Um, it doesn't matter when you come over, they're gonna keep, uh, fucking just drilling it and even if it's not true, they're gonna just keep poking and drilling and saying little things and twisting it and, uh, fake fucking bullshit.
So, you know, midnight, midnight is saying she doesn't know the backstory of your beef. Do you actually have a beef with the other with Crystal Ann?
Or you just
Well, I really don't but I really enjoyed Crystal Anne, but she
Keep saying that I'm a drug addict in that
Like all kinds of crazy shit about and and she says that she said I can't believe she's younger than me and look at her
I'm way older than her and I look better than her and I'm not a drug addict and she does a lot of drugs
And, um, so, you know, it's kind of like, you know, like, you know, you just want to and you don't want to beat, um, you don't want to kick a fucking blowfish.
You don't want to kick a blowfish.
I don't think I've ever heard that term.
But that's pretty good.
Yeah, I don't think I want to kick a blowfish.
No, it'll explode.
Yeah.
Bikes on the, on the outside wide so they might dig into your foot if you're not wearing shoes or anything, right?
Right blowfish have the have the spikes, right?
Um
Do both fish have spikes I think so. Hey, Darrell, I haven't seen you for a while. Oh
Fuck I don't fucking know dude
I just know that they look like
Like they're fucking cheeks are like like start falling apart and stuff
So is that why you don't want to kick them because their cheeks look like they're gonna fall apart?
Why don't you want to go? Let's get to that. Why don't you want to kick a blowfish that might help explain it?
There's a poison to water because it put oh, okay, okay
Okay
What
I don't even know Daryl. Why can't you talk to me like a normal motherfucker?
No, you can't because okay, let me tell you about Daryl
He doesn't talk to people. Okay. He only has to rap and he has his raps are terrible by the way
they're like
He's got a style, yeah
He's got his own style
Let's see if we can let's do a wrap-off Daryl
And the party left why do we fucking dig in at somebody ever was that
History's everybody's Darrell's coming at me. Let's see what Darrell has to fucking rap about. Let's see who's better Darrell
Come on up. They rip into each other man. Darrell
That is good days and bad days too like like the rest go. Hey Darrell Darrell show your rap, buddy
It's ridiculous
Everybody can understand him. He's a character. I'm not gonna say he he's like a normal person that that I see every day in my life
No, but he's a character and I like like when he comes around. I think he's funny
What can I say, you know each to their own true
like to see the humor in things man that that's the thing crystal yeah I would
like to see the humor and Daryl you know but Daryl just he can't even come up
with not even a one funny fucking line Daryl Daryl Daryl if I had a nickel for
every time I heard Daryl do you guys like not like each other or something like
is this an ongoing now he's just talking shit to me in the chat and then so here
the
Oh, you all you want to drop down and fuck him up in the China. Maybe two lovers alone. No, he's gone, dude. Oh
Thing is making the moves he's pulling the moves on you. Yeah, I'm about to go
Jamie get up here Jamie
And put the moves on you
Thing one's action. Well, is you be the Christine somebody he's passing now, you know
For action on the internet, okay everybody I cannot I don't see what he said what the fuck's the point
What's the point?
You know, I'm not looking for physical action on the internet. Yeah, you know, I keep my hanky-panky
Not on the internet. No
You don't want to be a frisky fellow on their covers
On the internet how does it
Saddest are seed. I don't I have no idea what you're talking about
what we said
Has well you have a
you're sincerely asking me a question, but I I don't see the question
What would we do we we just have what a camera back and forth and what I would
I took aviation class in high school
I thought we got in
How does that do the whole physical thing? It doesn't you're just jerking off doesn't
Exactly, that's why that's where that was physical thing. That's where they get that pilot thing about there you go. I
Never said I was a pilot
Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pamela. Pam
First time I didn't know what happened that answers your question. I
I mean, I went I didn't see your question though
But it was just hanging
There you go, there should have been babes there. You should have put moves on live woman instead of being up here with this
You know not this I was gonna say this cycle
Well, Christopher last night and put in the moves in there. That was last night
There you go. You didn't put the moves
There was a baby. Will you come up here? Somebody midnight?
Jamie they don't come up. Jamie doesn't come on panel may not doesn't go on panel
I've been a couple times with Jamie on panels. She does
That's a great occasion, bro
So I'm gonna count that out
voice Jamie
Jamie
Now you sound like Peter Jamie
Get up here Jamie fuck psyche psyche. I hate you. Oh, she's with someone right now
Contestants for what? We're guys planning here
What do you guys planning I
Can't see
Oh, midnight wants me to do a rap battle with Daryl.
Is that what you were saying? Oh, yeah, we should all do it.
Yo, Daryl sucks a dick from the beginning of the click.
What we can do without Daryl, because I heard you off.
You know, having teeth, dick.
I can set it off.
Daryl, Daryl, Daryl.
It sounds like barrel, the bottom of the barrel at that.
Come on
Barrel barrel barrel get up your barrel
We got it. No, see the thing is is that we got to get him
Started first maybe
So we can roast him to see where he's come
I only saw his one comment and then that was it. I've never I haven't seen him since
Was he hidden or he just did a drive-by and left no because he goes
I could do that too my name is Daryl
And I say I'm from another country and so I put up with you
But a bit of a do you heard that thing? I don't know. I don't but that's literally yeah, that's it's really
My jowls hanging holy shit without our jowls
So I can just jowls killin
Kind of like overlapping here like this this right there. That means you need college and cheeseburgers, bro
You know
Just me just get better, bro. Put on 30 pounds. Bye-bye job. Okay. No. Yeah, this is gravity. This is this is age
If you were a little pumpier a little more slumpier and the cheeks will plump up the jaws will be less
I guess we're 58. This is not bad. Look, I still
and the fucking cormorant brother
I'm not a fucker, you guys, I'm my period
and I am by by by
look at this age
40 fucking years
you have to double the calorie intake
you know how to say 12 calories a day
I was kind of exaggerating with the jowls
I was just saying like
I know I'm actually quite happy with the way I look at this age. I could look much worse
Yeah, no, you're right. You look good for your age if you are 58 or 68, whatever you are look good
I see you could pass with like late 30s 40s in my book. You look good, bro
There's no I know
That's why everybody everything everything I'm fucking I'm doing all the shit everyone's saying oh you she's getting to clubs for
People in their fifties
And I want to believe them my friend. I'm not interested for a woman in her fifties. Are you kidding me?
That's why like none of these things like apply to me things that are suggested to me are like
You just gotta you know, you're gonna find another person you raise that is
Harden looks younger than a race like you do. This is the whole thing. I don't want someone my age
Like I remember when I said I'm really picky
So what do you want younger older?
I don't want someone to fuck. I want a diamond pretty when I say youthful. I don't mean really young
I just mean not in their 50s. I mean 40s. Do you want page or fucking now crystal Marie basically?
Page of crystal marine youthful young 30s. I
Mean
Listen, bro, you can get 30s 35. I have a friend. That's my age and he's dating a 26 year old
You know, he's in his 40s 26 year old
That's not the point the point is love is love and you know and you have to know how to treat the person and whatever
That is an issue, like I realize that, I know, I know Alex, I know I can get, I know that
isn't my issue.
My issue isn't actually attracting what I want, my issue is actually
You know kind of like keeping them like making it a thing instead of just saying hi
I don't want to just be the friend. That's what I'm saying. That's where my issue is
You don't want to be in the friend zone and yeah, yeah, because that means no pussy 100% your friend
Exactly, I know I mean you can do it every now and then it's fine. There are some girls that you meet that are like
Yeah, you had girlfriend
Okay, do you want to know girlfriend like we're fucking be
Beta is someone that I I'd like her, you know, I like her as a friend. I'd like her I think she's you love her
I love a beat him just a minute
But I can't just do that forever.
I mean, there are some women that actually want to have
like a physical relationship with, right?
Yeah, well, she does.
You do.
And you're younger than you are.
And you kind of see me.
She was 51.
You're 58.
That's perfect.
I can't make the next move.
That's my issue.
But anyways, I want to talk about me.
I don't know.
Ask the baby come to Canada our father can't leave this hangout. Why not? What's the worst that can happen?
No, okay next at least you tried what's the best that can happen you fall in love and have the best life ever and
You know die together
The the juices were to squeeze bro. You're not gonna know until you try. That's the point
So just look at it like that. What's the worst that's gonna happen? I'm back here alone
What's the best
Days ago, okay, I was in I was in a really down state. Okay. I I
Hit a I hit a bump a few days later. I'm already feeling way better
You don't have to like do all this whole
You know making me feel good like I'm actually I'm okay. I understand I know what's going on
I know what I have to do. After this conversation,
I'm pretty excited. It's like you drop a beat.
I'm quite self-aware and insightful,
so I know what I need to do, and I'm moving.
I mean, she's hurting. Like, psyche drop a song.
I can't take it anymore.
What did she say? That's funny.
Well, she said after this conversation,
it's like you drop a beat. No, we're going to rap.
We're going to have a rap battle. We got to have a beat.
I
Think that is looking for love it could be crystal Marie
But maybe he's above what he's needing or wanting
Maybe he's gay and he was like he's cocked or maybe he was the doc
Okay, if I'm gonna do some free style can be nasty
you want to have a freak off baby psyche put us in the back it's freak off time me Marie and that thing over here
Absolutely not
Let's do it. I'm in I mean after three years fuck it. Let's do it. I'm done. I don't give a fuck anymore
Freak off in the back, baby
We need a bait
We can't play beats on I would play but I don't want to get you know, they can't do that. That's like
I don't want to like like you fucking think I
What are you gonna be there I
Don't fucking know those birds are killer thing. Yeah
Yeah, that's the worst when you're on the coke
I'm gonna go to bed you guys
I already want I already want to take off this sweatshirt. I'm already hot. I don't want to close the window, man. Oh
My god, do not show your nipples, bro
Crystal marine day equipment tonight three dreams my beautiful
Crystal Marie don't forget to unblock me in chat. No, I'm with her bro by the way
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
Well, then don't we can pull the sleep on the panel. Actually, I'm not leaving. I'm just gonna fall asleep
No, no, no, you said you were going. No, no, you can you can go. No, no, no
You know, thank you Roni's does
Before screen it's been great. It's such a good host tonight, but I think you can you can probably go Russ now
I think everything you want me to go and leave you guys alone. I'll do it. I got it. I'll be between the lines later, guys. I gotta go
Oh, I'm tired. I'm coming. I hear my mom calling. I gotta go. I gotta go
Crystal don't leave where you going? Oh my gosh
We go so tired. I was already it's like four o'clock in the morning
Five in the morning here is miss. Oh, wow is Missouri a time zone behind?
I'm maybe an hour that would be a time zone. Yeah
So what are you doing tomorrow Sunday or today
It's gonna tornado tomorrow, so we got it like you know, it's supposed to be 70 mile hour winds
I don't know my mom said she's
She might actually which she has a better basement than me. I don't even know why she wants to come over here
That makes no sense to me
Anyways
So you're gonna go no she's coming over here she wants to come but she's coming over here
Do you have a tornado like basement or whatever?
Yeah, tornado shelter. Yeah, but my mom's is a way fucking better. They wouldn't go to her place
She lives way further away. She lives almost two hours away, but she's gonna be in my area
So somebody in chat said that I'm adorable though
Oh, they did say though. So that would be like
Aside from all the bad shit. Yeah. Yeah, he's adorable though though
What does though mean?
What?
What does the though mean?
Though, it just means, you know, like though.
What do you do so?
No, no, though, like T-H-O-U-G.
I know, like why made what made her say though though?
That's what I'm saying.
As bad as I am, as terrible as I am, I'm adorable though.
you're not so though you're not a bad guy dude you're gonna contest that thank
you yeah you're not a bad guy give you that you're one of the good ones um what
do we got here one thing you like my new picture Jesus Christ why are you doing
that you're gonna get me in shit I don't like you know I've been fooled
It's my daughter's 13th birthday. Happy birthday to the 13 daughters of Paige.
You're supposed to grab your mattress over the top of your bathtub.
Why do you have a mattress over your bathtub?
Anyways, know the boy's grin. I was agreeing with thing.
Geez, stop it, Law.
The mattress over the bathtub.
So just my boy's grin. That's all. That's what it's adorable.
Oh.
Paige, I hope she had a great birthday. All 13.
Paige. Yeah. Oh happy birthday. Paige's 13 daughters had birthdays today. Oh wow.
Well happy birthday.
I have a birthday today.
My family actually have two birthdays in my family today.
Yeah.
So 13, do Native Canadians, Métis, do they have...
I'm kidding, Paige.
Do Métis, do they also have Bat Mitzvahs?
Bat Mitzvahs? Well...
Bat for women.
I think that's Jewish people.
Oh, I thought it was Métis.
I thought it was Native Canadians as well.
No, that's that's just for Jews
Yeah, that's just for Jewish men boys
Well boys are the bar mitzvahs women have bat mitzvahs, right?
I don't know anything about the Jewish people. Yeah
But
No, I'm you Jewish thing you dork
No, I'm you Jewish thing you dork. No, I'm you Jewish thing you dork
No, no like
What I have a no apostrophes or commas or anything. I don't know what the hell she's saying there
No, I'm you Jewish thing you dork that was Paige
That was one sentence from Paige new wish
No, I'm you Jewish thing you dork
She's saying that she's not Jewish
So why is she calling you a dork?
She's calling you a door. What the fuck paid you calling me a dork
And man is going midnight is going on about about tornadoes
dude
tornadoes dude
We had
Nine wasn't nine or was it I believe it was nine and one day
In like my area. Oh my gosh, but I think it ended up being like 12 or something, but nine hit down or some shit
Really? Oh, yeah, that was last week
Yes, and now a tomorrow or supposed to have a big one or bit
It's in my big one. It's actually not as strong as wins as last week. So I don't know
It's it's like 80 to 100 mile winds like the last week was in 114
But yeah, it was 75 so now that one said hey, I wonder why they do that I wonder who writes that I know who writes some of it but
I wish I could write some of that shit because some of these people are terrible
I need name names name exactly who's terrible tell me
Well, I'm saying different companies like you know like
One weather company will just be so different than the next but we're in the same area
And then they say that they're Kansas City weather
and then they are like out of Oklahoma
or they're out of like a different area
like Alabama or some shit.
So you really want to go with like our local
which is either Fox 4 or Channel 9, but.
So you're talking about tornado prediction
like within like a couple hours, right?
You're not talking about like a five day forecast.
Um, I'm talking about all together. They're all wrong. They're wrong every day. Well, you know, it's harder to do
Longer like the further on the future it is. It's harder to predict right the forecast. Oh
Yeah, of course. Okay, but I'm saying like this morning. It was supposed to rain and like fucking tornado all day
And it didn't do shit. No
Fuckers, how could they do that to you?
No, and then now they're saying it's tomorrow
fuckers
How are you gonna tell her so we're getting 80 mile winds one day we didn't get shit and then oh, sorry, we're wrong
It's gonna be tomorrow buds
Just expected
Expect disaster every day so that way yeah
We don't expect rain, expect snow, we don't expect a little sun.
I'm sorry I interrupted you. I don't, I don't even know what I'm saying.
I don't know what you just, I missed it, so I felt that. I need to go to the bathroom,
but if I were to get up right now, you're going to leave. No, go to the bathroom. No, but you're
No, I'm gonna talk to midnight. Okay. Talk to me
My gosh midnight you do not okay twister I
Remember twister back in the day and thinking it was like some good shit
Yeah, twister is some good shit. Oh my gosh, they don't even make things like that to work
I don't want to watch Twister too.
What did you say?
I mean, oh my gosh, um, man, I mean, you, like, if you could, like,
Find your love and then still have your car at the end a badass fucking vehicle by the way that bad-ass vehicle
Stay till the end
And she found a man. I mean
Twister was a great movie
Oh man, I wish I could see that
Yeah, twister with closing blankets, uh, we're gonna make well, it's probably gonna be storming all over the place
It's May. I mean it's gonna be raining
Oh, don't forget
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I was nice of her
Hey, you bram
She seems like a sweetheart
um
But she's in Florida, so that doesn't help me at all
Well Florida is a beautiful area. Oh, I'm not I'm not saying anything about that. I'm not in Florida though
Yeah, Florida is beautiful though
No, I know I know I just I'm saying I love Florida
Was I gonna say so where are you originally from are you from Missouri like originally a
Room, Texas, but yeah pretty much from Missouri
What does that mean you move there at a young age or yeah
When I was three
And then we, I mean, my whole family lives in Texas.
So it's just a couple of hours away, 1,000 miles away.
Well, 1,000 miles of this day,
these days doesn't mean much, right?
Yeah.
Do you get back there often?
I haven't lately, but yeah, I should, especially
Like my the end the others are getting really old. So yeah
what how
Where you are now in Missouri. Do you have?
Like what's the closest family that you have to you there?
Like are there meat? Are they immediate family or just distant? Yeah, just immediate. Yeah
I used to have cousins here, but
once or
You know once her parents start getting older they move back to Texas, so it's been kind of lonely. I will say
Cuz I had everybody, you know
Yeah
and like
Back and forth like months and all of our house, you know our
The family is like a free-for-all. You know, you just like you go and stay anywhere you want
You know what? I mean all you're gonna go to that
You know when you're in Texas you go in you go to so many places in Texas. You got so many places stay at you know in here
When they're here in Missouri, there's not that many places, you know what I mean?
And like we don't have fucking accountability. We don't have the space for
All our family, we don't live in mansions like they do
You're saying that your family in Texas lives in mansions. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
yep, I
Got good ones. I got bad ones. I got all of them
But yeah, when we stay there we stay with my peers and you know, you're all established and
Do you come from a well-off family I?
Mean middle class I guess it's pretty well off for middle class and being
From another country
Hang on I want to ask you another question, but before I do before this disappears. What are you talking about midnight?
Where is it?
Could you demonstrate some poses for us thing? What are you talking about?
anyways crystal I
Forget what my next question was. I think my next question was are you married?
He wants. Oh, I mean she wants you to do the reverse cowboy
Well, I need someone to demonstrate with me
Any
He volunteers like me. Oh
I'll do my part, but I can't play both roles
It's just the way it is
Midnight get up here
Midnight won't come up
As much as I like midnight she won't come up
Midnight, are you Karen?
Karen I will love you the same
I mean, midnight, if you're not.
So that's it. So no one wants to help do this demonstration.
No, you're not.
You guys don't want to help midnight at all.
Midnight is just, she's just curious and she just wants to know things.
She has it in causative mind.
And she's, she's asked her all the time and I'm willing to do my part to help her, but
to the rest of you with your selfish fucking concerns, man, you're all like, I don't want
to do that for midnight.
I don't want to look like a man from midnight.
I'm perfectly willing to demonstrate the, what was it?
Reverse cowboy.
Reverse cowgirl, sorry. Yeah. Oh
I
Will midnight I'll do my part
But I need I need you know, it takes two it takes two to reverse cow cowgirl I
Will say Karen is
Funny as fuck. Okay. You don't if you're saying Karen ain't funny midnight
Karen like I in X Karen
Yes, Karen has a sense of humor and it's funny as fuck. I think Karen's funny. I don't want to say anything about her
I mean, she's she's nuts, but that's all I'm gonna say. We shall call you magic thing. Okay
Magic like I'm the jokes everybody love everyone. Oh, he's so cute. He's adorable. Oh, we can joke with him
He's like always he's harmless. Oh my gosh your magic thing. Oh my gosh. I got it now
I forgot about cowgirls with him because he's harmless, right?
You wouldn't do this with some other dude. I didn't even know he'd be coming on to us
He'd be wanting to fuck us all. It's like no, did you know that magic thing was fucking roommates with
What
Which jacks from oh my gosh, what is that show called it's on the
Vanderpumper rules. I've never watched that. No
yes, magic thing was
Fucking roommates with jacks from Vanderpumper rules
Never watch it. I don't know like is that a good thing or bad thing what it's just a thing. It's just a thing
Let's smash getting all over my ass magic thing lol. I mean night. It's fine. I'm sorry. I
Think Karen's money
You're not Karen and I'm sorry I called you Karen, you know, I need my cat after you
You know what midnight midnight? I think somebody else. That's not Karen is Karen
I mean, that's how bizarre this is when I talk to midnight I call and I have this thing I have
Sorry, I had something stuck up my nose
Stuck up your nose
You're doing those those big nasal inhalers while you're talking. I have allergies dude. It's getting a fucking I
Couldn't do everything at once. I
Can't breathe at a one. I
Can't breathe and talk at the same time
It's one of those inhalers, you know, it's really nostril.
Fix inhalers. Remember they're white and they've got like the little holes on the end you go
you know
You know with them
I remember those. Yeah, you stick it up your nose so you can
Yeah, it's it's it is a tampon. It's a tampon for your nose
And no, I don't got nosebleeds
You did you see blood on it you weirdo?
I just, um,
just get a rate of storm and got the allergy
to the alcohol and the fucking storm.
Did the allergy to the alcohol to the storm?
No, I have an allergy, like an
alcohol-allergic thingy.
Or every time I drink one of my nostrils close up,
Or not like after two drinks sometimes I both do it depends on if I'm drinking my car
What happens if you have the third drink after that then it clears up
So it's like it's a toggle switch. Yes
But right before I get to go to bed it gets really bad
And that's when I got to start doing the nasally thingy so I can, you know, breathe in the morning so I can get the fuck up and do some fucking exercise and get my day going.
What do you do in the, when you wake up usually?
Gristel.
I run.
Do you?
Yes.
I tried that. I took up jogging for a bit in my like
30s fucking hated it. I did it for like two weeks. I'm just like fuck this. Why am I doing this? I
Wonder why I'm doing it now
Anything I should be doing it now now is the time. No, I feel like I need to because I don't want to get like soggy
Yeah, I don't want to get like trash. Did you see Trash show on her body off? She's also like skinny and was soggy
who I
Don't get me involved with this shit man. Don't start calling everybody fucking
I'm just saying
Just saying you know I've been doing this for a while like that's even the more the Mary the reason why like I don't want to be
Like a fucking soggy looking fucking
person
Yeah, I don't want soggy
I'm a firm nice and firm
Yeah, you don't want soggy when somebody you and you look down
You know when you look at page you see you see sports
you see
golf. Is that what I see? When I see Paige? Well, I do. I see a golf club. About the smack
up bitch in the yapper. I don't know. I see her holding one of those electrical, you know,
Just zapping people as they go by. Hi, love you back. Hi
Hi, everything's great. Things will be great when you when you know, that's that's how I see page
Packy a'slef up
I don't want people to see this is like a weaker socky person or you know when I when I seen that video of traction, I was thinking, dang.
She is so skinny and how could she be so floppy why you guys over why are you so catty is it just just because
No trash it trash is like been she uses she's been me for years
She's profile pictures of me. She does weird shit. She sends videos out as me
She said pussy pics. She said pussy videos instead. It was me
Okay, no, I have a fucking issue with this bitch wait where are these videos?
She sent them to multiple people. I mean I didn't get them
Anyways go on psych psych if you if you're up backstage, okay? Someone's backstage go on Christmas. Are you sorry? I
Say that because Kelly's been covering her and I watched Kelly
Okay
The last weekend she got really drunk and drove with her kid
You said this already. Yeah, I don't know about this you
And she got naked
And she was dancing in front of her child
Okay, and she was dancing right and her belly was flopping around but she's so skinny. How can you be so skinny?
I don't know, I just maybe want to work out more
And I was like, oh shit. I got me. I'm making me want to double my workout
I'm gonna take 90 minutes to fucking
I haven't been doing 90 minutes
Hey, wait, when you wake up, you said that you jog how far do you jog when you wake up? I have a treadmill and I have an elliptical
You have a treadmill and then an elliptical what I?
Go for 90 minutes
Wait, what's the elliptical wait? I need to know what that is
Ellipticals when you kind of like it's like a roundabout
So you have a tiny track in a room
That one's upstairs
In my
I think it's so old too
That that's why I got like a treadmill because the fucking ellipticals like 20 years old
I got it for my brother's like the fucking ex-girlfriend
Literally like 20 years ago
The elliptical is a stand-up thingy with handles that you run on yeah, it goes on like a circle-ish motion. Yeah
like
And then, but I've been using the treadmill and I've been going at seven at seven speed, which is the fucking I go at seven six is the fastest I have on this thing and I spend $100 on it, which is like, nothing for what I've been using it for.
But, um, I go on manual I set up on manual for 100 minutes.
And so I usually go 90 and then I'm like fucking
If I do 10 more it'll be after eight or when I'm like
Like about to go to bed or something 90 minutes is okay, but that extra 10 is just fuck that that'll destroy you man
It's hard Jamie. It is so hard to get motivated
I'm telling you what
The best thing for me is to turn my phone off. I
have to turn my phone off and
Just put music on like and that's it when you're running when you're doing the treadmill or whatever. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, that's the best is to
Put yourself out of the moment
So it's like it's like when you're driving like a long distance and like before you know it like an hour's gone by
You're like, I don't even remember driving that last hour
It's like that kind of thing
Yeah, I started at three. I started at three by the way flip flap
I started at three which people were telling me. I was crazy for starting at three
Is that when you get like you are crazy for starting at three?
Man, I run so fucking fast though. I was like, what do you like it's like I have long legs. What do you want me to do? It's like
I do little steps. I try to like make them different too. Oh
Sorry, I was talking to flip flat in the chat
Yeah, I know I know it's nuts
You know why is because I've been pushing myself because it's like I feel like I'm not doing enough and
Like sometimes I'm like shit
If something happens and I can only get in 30 minutes,
I'm gonna go as hard as I can
and I can always go the extra time.
You know what I mean?
Why it goes so hard is beyond me,
but I have to go so hard at everything I do in life.
Everything?
Pretty much.
I mean, I'm clean.
Yes, I'm a clean fanatic.
My nose is stuffy. You don't even know how many no stuffies. I have
So many un-stuffies in none of them fucking work, okay, this is the best one the ones that stick right up your nose is the best
Obviously
Okay, now let's let's get back to you saying that everything you do you go like a hundred and ten percent at you you go hard
I don't go on. I just try to
Try doesn't mean I said succeed at everything. I did you give it a hell of an effort. So let's talk about that again
everything
Pretty yeah, I think so. I mean I'm like fucking man. You should see my yard
Yeah
Because it's a lot of work I don't care. I'm not interested in your yard. Oh
Then I please midnight
So all of a sudden see now now I'm becoming an issue right because now it's like oh
But any other time I'm just a nice guy. Yeah, things not dangerous you are a nice guy. Oh my god, oh
Right. Oh my god. Oh
By the way, I watched this fucking movie tonight. Oh, sorry, which one?
Well, I had to say it so aggressively, so I had to like take it back
I don't care which movie did you watch? I watched um the new anaconda with Jack Black
Why oh?
It was so good. I
Was so funny and it reminded me you know that I talked with my
Me and my sister talk to each other with our toes. We shoot these fights
Your sister talked to each other with your toes
Yes, we point with our toes and we yell at it. We can point at each other
We can plop money with their toes. We can yell at each other. We can really point at each other with our toes
Holds your sister. I can pull you my at my sister with my toe
Hell I'm nine years older than me. I don't even care if she's single
Oh, no, no, my son that oh, no, did she six years old? Oh, yeah, she's six years. All right. Oh my god
Sorry, sis. Oh my god. I always age her
Oh
Oh, I got so many bros, you know
Is she part of the community at all your sister, okay, that's probably for the best
No, my family would fucking kill you guys in real life
No
Yeah, they were
I'm not fucking around. I swear to God. I swear to God on everything. I love
Yeah, if they find out who some of these motherfuckers are they're gone
And that's fucking facts
And they don't even care they would fucking rot dude
They would fucking rather rot than ever let somebody disrespect me. Oh my god. Bye Jamie
I'm sorry
You're saying that that they would rather like rot in jail or something like that. Oh, yeah, they've already done time
They've already murdered people
Yeah, I got a bunch of them that murdered people
People is that what you're saying right now? I got them all over the place. Yes
I got a cousin that came down
Just to fuck somebody over right when he got out of prison. Can you hear me just to go back?
I can hear you Jamie. Good. I downloaded that app
What
That app before remember it takes you to the studio. Oh
Sorry, I can tell you're talking, but I can't hear what you're saying
Hi crystal
I had downloaded that app the right way remember and it takes me right to it
Which one the streamers? Yeah, remember kicking me off that one-time page come up
I love you so much, Jamie. You're so great.
So cute. Midnight. Sadie.
Let's go through the chat, guys.
Oh, my gosh. Jamie, you have such a beautiful voice and you're such a beautiful human.
It looks like I'm alone with, like, all the ladies tonight.
Like, I just see ladies in chat from as far as I know.
Sean.
Right? Like, this is...
Midnight. You have no idea because...
Katie, you know, I'm gonna retaliate and I told fucking clumsy. What's gonna happen before it happened?
But that old video of him fucking trying to sell his nieces to good times
It's going on a big
Stringer one of all and it's gonna be out there
Because he kept fucking fucking with me. He kept putting my face out there. I kept telling him to stop it
I kept telling him to stop messing with me. I'm gonna do something really
He's gonna fucking regret because I'm gonna put his face out there and he's literally as a predator
page okay
She's got a call she said
What are you going on about crystal?
Yeah, Crystal, who are we talking about?
Oh, Clumsy, he edits photos of me, and he likes to use them.
Because he knows it bothers you.
Right, right.
But let's see, the thing is, is that he's done some really nasty things to me prior.
And I got all that shit on recording. I don't need to tell you guys what he did because the thing is is that it's better for the fucking
Shit that is gonna happen to him in the long run, but
What I'm saying is that what I want to get him in because he wants to fucking use my shit and he wants to use pictures of me
He edits me right he edited my fucking head
It's not funny dude. It's not funny for females. I was a model dude. This guy makes me he pretty yellows my teeth
They make some look bad here. He fucking crooked to my baby. He doesn't really bad things
So does my kids like he's done the same shit. He's made me as Kim
In which I love him. I don't want to fucking
They try to make a like that's like a bad thing like I fucking disrespect Kim like
Um, but the thing is is that they're trying to make me somebody that I'm not, okay?
Okay, and the fact is is that I'm gonna make them prove who they are
Okay, because I have video
proof of
Clumsy being a fucking weirdo
Many times and he keeps fucking doing weird shit
Well, why do they why does he care about me? I don't know why you guys hold these grudges and these fucking
Longstanding feuds. I don't know. I don't know why I didn't know about it. Yeah
Yeah, that guy's been on some weird shit, I just want people to get along one day, you know, but
Yeah, never say never
Yeah, never say never. I mean, I will say never with clumsy because I will never
It's he's on the same with Brandon Q for me because I seen what he did and you guys didn't but I have it
It's going it's going to be bigger because I want it to be retaliated. I'm all new to the person. So
All right
That was my that was my anger of snot
Did you just booger down your face like yeah
If he was there with a burger this fucking head
Crystal earlier with the sunglasses
I spilled out your name with the sunglasses because it's super star right?
Oh you did?
I didn't see that.
It's like you got erased or something and I'm like what the fuck that took a long time
bitch.
Oh my gosh.
I'll have to do it again.
Thank you so much.
Oh my gosh I didn't even see it.
I was paying attention too.
You know, I ain't the I ain't the brightest time. I can lie to anybody
I tell these people like midnight soft limits at this, you know
Channel or wherever I'm at and they don't listen. It's like dude
just
There are she's off limits, right? They don't listen to me
Midnight pushes it though. Midnight pushes it, but I
Like I know, you know, she has her good nights and bad nights. I get it
But sometimes when you give her some leniency like when I ask a channel person, yeah, just just let her go
She's cool
She doesn't on purpose she she tests it to get you in trouble
No, not fucking. Yeah. Yeah for vouching for yeah. Yeah, I don't care
Oh midnight. I will fucking die for midnight. Yeah, they never listen, huh?
You know how many times I've votes for midnight on page on Sykes?
You know how many times you know how many times she still gets blocked even though I fucking votes for her?
I know!
I hate that, Sykes.
I know, I try.
I mean, I'm not saying that like, uh, you know what I'm saying midnight
I'm not saying like I just I love the fuck out of midnight midnight is like
The other
Well, it's Jamie. You're amazing as well. I mean, I love you both
Yeah, you guys are both really great to me
I'm not like easy to like
I
Know I make it like I don't want these because I don't like these people are not nice people. I mean they're not like
You don't really want it. I don't know
You just know everything that you've been taught and it's like you know like the things like and then you just can't do too far
And it was like some people you just like
But midnight doesn't get she doesn't get that far right no never
We should ask some channel owners if midnight ever gets
Don't think so. She certainly gets hidden a lot. Yeah, I don't know why
Same with that douche weed person
Have you ever seen midnight gets hidden because
I mean, I doesn't like like the norm like she doesn't like to
You know go with like the majority of the group or just be there on you know, just
like to be their own person just
When you are a different
Human it's not good in this environment like pages in the back
I like to go on my own way. Midnight hilarious
cycle page up. Oh
My god, I'm gonna burn some sage first
page
I'm gonna burn some sage
my dog page
Those birds man, my god, they don't start us. They don't stop they started like three o'clock three thirty and they just keep going and going and going
What is it?
They're nice to listen to.
Whatever they are, I don't know, what are they?
Sparrels? I don't know.
I don't have to ask Paige.
I don't know.
Oh, you do have birds all day all night.
No, Paige, hurry up and get up here.
What is that about that is amazing? I don't know. I remember I remember the birds used to start around
Dawn like maybe you know five ish and then later, but now they're they're going off it like yeah
Yeah, you would literally have birds all day all night
Don't listen to them. They don't think that drives me nuts
Are they chickadees? Yeah, she just said that I told you she would know
Yeah, why are we taking pages word for it? Because I agree with her page because it's page she wouldn't
I'm sure she knows I would burn in the world page doesn't live in my neighborhood she doesn't know
oh yeah she knows she doesn't know
I don't have a bird of chickadees in my she's a whisperer. Yes. She's a whisperer
Oh my god. What is it? Oh, yeah, you're burning sage again
That looks pretty cool. Why is it purple? Is that just what happens or my sage? My cat takes off with it
Yes, we're lighting. It does look a little purplish. Yeah, he loves it. I
Don't want to
Making I gotta clean what are you saying Arthur it like
Everyone in Canada is in Pages DMs. Is that what you're saying? I don't think Pages like that
Everyone here, maybe everyone but me
Does she know McFrosty McFrosty the hell is McFrosty?
You know what Chris, you can't ask him any movies. I've been asking him for like these well McFrosty is he was he
he ran for mayor of
Uh, uh, liver, not liver, uh, what is it called?
Wilming, not Wilming, uh, where is she from?
It's from her area.
Who?
Willing.
Willing?
She's in Alberta.
Alberta, but yes, it's Alberta, it's next to Alberta.
He lived in Alberta
Romania
Well, it's like Willington or something or we're going to bet to bet
No, it's in the same state. It's like
Just Alberta. Oh, you mean the Paul is it the Tetris King? Yeah. Yeah
Yes, oh
My gosh, you guys can see my dishes. I'm so sorry
Page one I didn't know I saw my thing on
Hmm I don't have that many dishes. I just have like who cares I just have like one
Who's frosty? Wait, wait. Yeah, we still haven't gotten to it
Frosty can't live in Ontario
Yeah
Cornwall that's it
Cornwall cornwall shut up. No one lives there. Yeah, he ran for mayor
Yeah, like not really they kind of got close he was like number three
Cornwall
McFrosty mayor
He ran. He's not the mayor. He ran
Regarding the frosty query Jordan
MC. Oh frosty. Yes, there he is. There he is
Wait, this is fucked up. Oh, do you
Look frosty
He was trying to get the changes. You know what everything he wanted changed
I don't know he won
At the end of the day he won this is ridiculous
This is one of the end of the day he won
He asked for changes that he won. No, there's no fucking emcee frosty in our parliament. Shut the fuck up
Mick frosty whatever. There's no Mick frosty in our parliament. It's blurry
MC
MC Frosty!
MC!
Yeah, he did run for mayor, dude.
Yeah?
He didn't do it, he didn't do it this year.
We had a fucking crack mayor here too, man, so what?
The almost
Hey Crystal, I wasn't gonna give that anaconda movie a chance, but it is hilarious. Oh my gosh, isn't wasn't it good?
Yeah, I have an Amazon stick jail broke. I did it myself and yeah, so it was good
Yeah, I watched that one
Yeah, Paige you remember Rob
Now his brother is the premier of Ontario. I mean if these people don't have these things like at their house
I don't know what's taken so long because
you know
Just free airwaves
The Amazon stick
In the Amazon you can jailbreak it
And you can literally get in the Amazon
That that movie should be movie of the year, sorry it was good me and I hadn't watched a good movie in a while
But I actually did watch a good movie
Yeah, I heard about that. Shall I share at least they're on right? Yeah, she really got hurt doing that, but it's almost like
That I don't know how honestly because it was so AI I don't see how
That's what they said. Yeah, I
Don't see how she really got hurt, but I
Mean she must have gotten hit in the head for real
or something. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I heard about that. And the other one is screen seven. I wasn't
going to give it a try, but it wasn't bad. Oh, man. I hadn't seen that one yet. That one went
bad. You got an Amazon. You have to jailbreak it. I can. Yeah, I got that one. I have Amazon.
Yeah, but is it? I have Amazon in the Amazon. No, I'm just kidding. I'm sure I do.
I don't know. I just you can get all the movies at home like all your
movie movies at home. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I watch yeah, I use the Amazon Prime thing for the movies Alex. I have not stopped
right
But they're all not out the door and you can like Joe break it yourself
Yeah
Man, I thought that was pretty funny at the end where fucking J. Lo showed up and she was like
Oh, sorry
Nevermind
Oh, no. Yeah, but Jack Black. Do you like how they put him out there? And they thought he was dead and he was running with that. Oh my gosh, he was like, that is so funny.
Oh my God. And then they was like, whoever thought of the dead squirrel in my mouth was sweet.
What is that? You're just
Yeah, she told the ending.
What? Never mind. Sorry. Sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, I'm just a regular going
to the toilet and shut up.
Well, because you guys want
Well, let's hear it for Nicki
Oh my gosh, what do you guys think about all the scientists you know this really is kind of scary to me because
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I heard about that. Mm-hmm that Nancy Grace was talking about that
On Fox news
How do you think about it strings strings
scientists disappeared died
Fucking
Supposedly killed themselves from the back
Oh, yeah, it's just weird shit, isn't it thing?
I don't know some of it's absolute absolute bullshit some of it is questionable. I don't know I can't explain it
But some of it's absolute bullshit
So we're not taking him to
No, that it's something nefarious, but it's not
Let's go to skin Walker ranch that'd be good skin Walker ranch. That's like on my bucket list with yeah
Skin Walker ranch is connected to this well because we're talking paranormal
I don't think yeah page. Hello page. That would be so fun. Well, what is it? What is it? Is it?
Everything
What could it be? I mean, is it it's either another country or government or aliens?
You fucking pick. You fucking pick things. You fucking pick things. You fucking pick things.
You want to pick an alien? You want to pick the government? Or do you want to pick your fucking government, bitch?
It's your choice.
I just think it's another way to attack the institutions to take down any kind of science, any kind of authority when it comes to that kind of thing.
That's what this is. It's just another attack vector on institutions.
So you think it's oh, it was an attack of that woman's hands being radiated and
She was getting recorded and saying that she was gonna she was scared
She was gonna get killed because she found out too much information that she shouldn't have known but she was scared
She couldn't tell anybody because she found it fucking out
And then she dies and her boyfriend fucking dies she makes a post before it to
Before and says it shows the radiation on her fucking hands and says it's going into her fucking
They're they're doing all the same
Operating the stuff like you actually look for evidence that this this actually
Yes, yeah, have you yeah, I usually do yeah, I don't think you have because you didn't know about that
I just know that some of these scientists that that are missing are fucking crackpots that
More than likely just up themselves and are like setting some kind of narrow. What kind of
What you know, I know two scientists
And they're not crackpots they might be a real
Scientists are I'm saying some of the ones that that appear on this list some of the ones that got this whole ball rolling
are people that probably off themselves,
but we're paranoid, but we're paranoid in actual life.
She's one of the people that help cure AIDS, okay?
One of my best friends in the entire world.
I don't think AIDS has been cured, but okay.
It is, it has, sorry, you're retarded.
Okay.
But...
My friends hear that she's a scientist
And she's had weird shit happen to her you don't even know we've had to watch her back
She had have us fucking watch her back for her
There are times that she was scared. She stayed in my house for weeks
Okay
I can get started, but I'm doing like fucking she's doing like some weird shit with
With blood she was doing blood work like she was the like doing scientists like she like with bloods
The blood
This is in
Does anyone wind up you don't think I see that shit all the time
No, yeah, my my friend though is, uh, she like you go to Stockton and it's like you have to like, yeah, you have to make sure you know where you're at.
Well, she's a she's a scientist. You know, she works. She's a doctor that works for KU. She's a she's an actual.
Teacher now, but she's not
And trust me she is not smart, okay? I mean she's smart
Yeah
Yeah, you know they're
Asking people to like if they want to give blood or something to donate make sure you didn't have the shot
It's like who the fuck took the shot
It actually like I don't want to get started on it, but it was all planned and it was never real
Well, you know like when I was younger
There's there's things that really don't fuck with me right now or fucking with me because I did
Work with I don't I can't even talk about not better. I better not do all that shut down our fucking, California for a year
Idiots right midnight idiots
But I didn't work with political people and
It did have a lot to
It was kind of weird in a sense
They were like we were like political models me my bro and my brother or my brother's girlfriend
But we've seen a lot of shit and I'm so thankful for that time that I was like a never drink because man, dude
Those people were weird as fuck I can't even talk about it. I can't even talk about it
I don't even know what the fuck is going on right now. What are you discussing?
You're just saying we weren't for a political party, you know, we're kind of like, okay
There is like, okay, I will say that there's okay
That's going on right now in the news. There's somebody that's pretty fucking young, right?
It's too political for everybody and it's it's it's even for me to even
Put together that I was
Midnight, no, he's blue. I don't even want to even know
You guys midnight
Okay, I don't look at details in the years. I still see headlines, but you guys are fucking crazy down there, man
It's not like I'm just yeah, America your politic your politics are fucking nuts
Again, this is not like I'm just realizing this
This is from decades of no our president was smart before he fucking got
Me nip
I'm seeing your politics is they turned him into an alien. He's retarded
Fucking the psyche. He's a fucking retard. He's a fucking everybody that fucking believes in all this weird shit
Alex put your pole down. I'm not sweepy at all. Stop. I hate that. Please you guys
Did you see what psyche the psyche you really need to get that fucking?
Codex shit because I'm telling you I'm gonna sue your ass. You were lying all over my fucking name, dude
Yeah, he's fucking quoting me for shit. I never said he is like literally
Quoting like middle conversations as me
Well, he's trying to make me he's trying to make me look stupid as fuck
And it's the AI right pulling shit out of the
What's it called? Yeah, he's not he did not look at that
I don't want to be in his codex, and I'm gonna sue his fucking ass
hmm I
Don't want to be in some codex that he is lying about me like dude. It said
I was trying to say that, um, a guy with, uh, like it didn't even say it correctly because I was,
you know, like you can't expect AI to do everything for you.
Okay, so he was saying that, okay, um, on there one of my quotes was like,
Um, a man with two hearts and with one small heart is whatever
Christmas good to see you
Yeah, I saw that too. Yeah, what a fucking did you see what he did to me?
He did everything disrespectful. None of those quotes are anything that I fucking quoted
Who what are you talking about now? I'm totally lost
What the hell is going on?
Then I stop the conversation
Sorry about that
but what he did is he let other people quote
um like and oh what is this oh what is that
oh my gosh this unlike as it was my quote like what a fucking weirdo i don't
want to be in his book i don't i'm gonna sue his
ass i'm suing him he's gonna have a big
Don't know
Okay, what he dropped the link already. I see it
Hello
Hey page he didn't have one fucking thing to say
Miss he didn't have one thing to say about
What is happening?
What are you talking about a boot? Yeah, what are you talking about?
Even I caught that
He's removing me he's removing me
Crystal, you're moving me every time I talk
But why are you spazzing out all of a sudden on the fucking transcript shit? You know that it's AI pulling the shit, right?
It's no hundred percent accurate crystals. So if it isn't there is a fuck-up. It probably you know, that's that's what I'm telling
That's what I'm telling good times as a k a fucking psyche
Way to say that he is he is getting his quotes wrong
His quotes are all wrong
He has never quoted me correctly, and he's never even mentioned
page in all of his fucking writings when page has been nothing but kind and
Very
Everyone has been
uh, categorized, documented, however you want to say it.
He's getting around to it.
Well, Dave should be uplifting, and she should be giving, uh, fucking uplifting.
Maybe. Maybe he hasn't got there yet. You never know. I'll give him some time.
Yeah, maybe he's not there yet.
Oh, but he, uh, he gave, uh, nine, or nine segments to fucking, uh, quotes that I didn't even say.
That we're AI he didn't even check him remember though, hon. I haven't been a part of the community
You didn't check this clothes. He didn't even check the quotes
Well sake he better open to be better be open to suggestion
Yeah, that's all I can say about it, right?
But what do we say about that because he's not being nice to me and he's not you freaking out
She's just getting it off her shoulders. Let her talk for a sec. She's not being a jerk. She's just stating her
I just have a loud voice. I'm sorry. I have was like one nostril
So I feel like I have to talk louder
Okay
I'm so sorry. Okay. I'll talk
Hold on. Let me blow my nose. Okay
When I blow my nose I can hear you guys
Yeah, because our ears and our nose like our sign of cavities connected to our ear canal
So like it is just it's a whole thing Paige, you know Alex is crazy
Thinking I'm somebody else
Fuck people's opinions
I know
Sweepie and I know Jamie personally like like have video time with both of them
Yeah, you don't know a sweepie sweepie is not a nice person like you are they're not the same people though
They're like, they're not the same not the same. Yeah
Sweepie is not a nice person like Paige you are a good person
Okay, you don't give a fuck what other people say you're just looking wrong with the fucking bunches, okay?
I like Sweet Pea Crystal.
I think she's nice.
I mean, everybody's got their
is she really nice when she
pretends to be nice to everybody
and she makes fucking A.I.s on everybody.
And then if you fucking say anything,
a whole team comes after you.
Paige, have you ever noticed that?
I do notice the activities.
Yeah, but they can make, um, oh, and then, and then guess what happens, Paige?
She's in the hospital. She's a sick fucking fat whore.
Oh, oh, oh.
Who the fuck is she going up there? What was that?
Come on now.
Was she going at you, Paige?
No, no, no, no, no, but still.
Absolutely not.
Who's a fat whore?
Sweepy.
Sweep he's not fat. She's not fat. No, and she's not she's not. Yeah, she is
I don't know, but she's not fat. Yeah, she is she actually is and she's actually not
Like I've actually yeah, I've actually seen what she looks like and she's not fine. Yeah
Yeah, I think yeah, I am pretty sure we smell the fat in her voice. Yeah, she's pretty fat
I'm sorry guys. She might use something for you guys. She might use a cover-up, but yeah, I know who she is
Hey, we're not all going to get along on here, but I mean, like, you know, when we, I base my opinion on everybody, but what I experience with them, not what the York, like others experiences with them are, I mean, to an extent, yeah, but she makes fucking, I never even said she was bad, I never even knew who she was or said anything about this fucking.
Fucking fat fucking or until she started mentioning me. Okay. She started making videos on me
What and now yeah? Yeah, she started making videos and she made me a fat person. Okay, so
Let me tell you I'm doing the same thing back
It's this true or no. Oh, yeah, she made me with black hair and a Chinese like
Like like she's trying to make me Mexican, but she made me like I don't know what the fuck she was trying
I don't think so if that's the same picture that everybody was going off the boat that like
Yeah
I'm sorry page. I'm sorry page. She tried to make me fat as well, and I'm not she's fat her breath is fat
I'm sorry. I've seen her. I've seen her. You can make up all you want to. I've seen the fucking shit
I'm sorry. I mean you guys you can have your opinions. I just I like her don't color horror, please. That's not nice
I've seen her and I've seen what she does to dudes too have you ever seen what she did like you don't know
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what does she do dudes is it sucks to me like we talked we are we're friends in like real life
So like I do know her like she's not she's not a whore
I'm sure you are fake friends with her in real life. You guys like bully and uh gang up on each other
You guys
Where you guys like to call each other and just hit up one fucking female
Yes
Well, you know, um, you can call it what you want to, you can call it ganging up, you can call it, uh, one on nothing, uh, because you won't go one on one. Now you are. But what do you mean? I won't one on one. What the fuck are you going off about? Yes, I will. And I'm not scared of nobody. And also, I do like all of you. So I don't have a problem with anybody. So don't confrontate at all. So I'm not really, this isn't, this is, this is false.
Well, I'm sorry that I feel that way about you, but I don't
Why are you being like this crystal is it bad nice? Yeah? Yeah, because Sweepie's actually
Sweepie so Sweepie are you talking about Sweepie who you've been talking about all this time? Yeah?
She's a scumbag. Do you don't know her?
They don't like me, but guess what? I don't pick sides and that's what page is I don't yeah
I don't pick sides and I'll stick up for all and I'm not talking about page ever. I would never talk about you page
I think you're a beautiful person
Well, I like you too, Crystal. I
Think you're fucking brilliant, dude
You do everything correct you do it right
Sorry, I didn't mean to confrontate with you. I just didn't want you to say that about Sweet Pea
But like I said, you're gonna have your own opinions and I mean
I don't like to get in the middle of anything, but I would never bully anybody and especially I'm not I don't have anything against any of you
Yeah, well, I don't believe you and I know how it is when I'm in that situation
So it is what it is. I'm not in a situation. This is page. Okay page. I was there. He's stupid whore
Hey, what? Crystal, watch your fuckin' mouth, bitch. Second of all, I don't have a problem with you. Now I do.
What is going on right now? Do you want to talk about it, please? Because this is so crazy.
Please don't talk to Paige like that.
This is insane. I care, I like, I don't have a problem with you at all.
Anyways, I just came up to ask me to you, but I got other
You know what I just you know what I was nice and then you know what if somebody can't do their wrongs
Then I don't want to fuck with them. You know what if somebody ain't gonna do their wrongs back then go fuck yourself page. I
Will and I'll do it really well. Thanks, Crystal. I'm gonna do it right now
See you later. Thanks for the reading the other night is great
You think so Arthur what exactly it do I have a front seat to I
Don't know what the hell's going on. I can't I can't deal with
How's this the best seat
Jamie I love you Jamie Jamie
The reason that I appreciate you because you fucking you hold your own and you fucking don't like let these motherfuckers
Southern like I know what's going on, and I know how it works, and I know
Where this person lies, and I know where other people lie, and I know how these things go
Yeah, but no, oh
Okay, and that is yeah, yeah, okay
Okay, Arthur, in that case, fine, but I need to see some rolling around. I need to see some oil, some mud, something, some skin.
Come on, ladies. Let's get to it.
I don't like it going on, and I don't like it in the middle of it, but...
That's not what we were getting at.
Where did Paige go? Aw.
Aw, I know.
You think maybe one day?
That's not where I was going
when that she would
Say that her rocks too because she was bullied to me and her and her fucking stupid fucking whore friends
bully me
Okay, so
I want, I want her to, uh, fuckin' apologize to me.
I'm not gonna be the only one apologizing here.
I'm not the only one in the wrong here, okay?
Those whores paid really bad shit to me.
And by the way, I've known of Paige for longer than she fuckin' even knows because she's been doing weird shit to me.
So, and her and her fuckin' stupid Christine fuckin' crackhead friend.
on this is anyways and guess what Christine is gonna go to prison I just
hate all the fighting yeah Christine is abused yet we found at least 10 victims
are going to press charges against her and I'm going to do it too and I'm going to be
like oh we're all here let's just all press charges against Christine
What's going on
Crystal you're still going you were you were gonna go to bed like I know
Like an hour ago or something like that man. I told you Jamie joined. I'd stay up
We're Chris. I mean not in a crystal
What's your face? What's what's the girl from Canada? What?
What you forgot
I'm just playing around I did that the other night. Oh, you're not even I did it the other night, too
I'm playing around. I love page. I'm kidding. Wait. I spoke in the door page, dude page
But these people
Paige has the energy of these other people you just went after Paige and now you like her
Me no crystal. Yeah, I know
Me crystals insane though. We knew that now you I said that
Well, can we bring her back up?
You could do whatever you want to I mean, I love Paige. I never said I didn't like her
I told you guys that it was like her fucking stupid fucking people. I never said it was her
Yes, I did
That hurts me though I
Man, but
I don't know dude. I don't know dude. I don't like these people dude. They all give me the bad feelings
Not page mm-hmm, but not page though, but not page. I mean not really I
Wanted page up here
But I'm gonna get that. I'm so sorry. I I fucked it up. I like I apologize
Yeah, tell her they
I'm so sorry page, you know, it's
How I don't I don't know how you called her a whore, that's right
Only fucking who has called her for me. You're on the same level as because she triggered me
I told you you trope fucking triggered me
Is she can't handle me Connor or I don't think she I didn't even do it like me Lee
She doesn't get in the middle of anything and she's fair and she just couldn't handle like one word
or
Because that's all how come on pages sweetheart, you know that crystal I
Love I mean I love page
Why why go to that level pages not like what do you guys try to you guys are trying to make me like
Seriously
Call her a fucking call her corny or something cuz she's corny like beyond belief. She's just like
I'm getting
We're trying to fuck every fucking dude in the fucking industry we're done
Crystal what are you saying?
Are you gonna be nice to her though, really?
What the fuck you guys want?
What do you want me to say, bitch?
Why are you going on her like that?
Yeah, you guys want me to tell you guys want me to show you. Yeah
So we're gonna bring Paige back up if you're nice
Yeah, she's gonna show herself to Bruno and to plug in a bunch out there bugging
to Aldi and to
She can put on a bikini and run around again. Oh page do it do it for the chat. Could you do it for the chat this time?
Except for personal people
I'm not
Nifty nickel you shut the fuck up nifty nickel you don't even know shit
Nifty nickel you need to get your fucking shit together
Oh my gosh
I don't need their page. I really don't know
What I'm just answering page and chat what a page say calm when you want I don't give a shit
I have no idea what these people I don't even know who these people are either. I love page
Peach don't worry about it crystals on one could this is how she gets page page
This is how she gets no one no one's gonna take it. What does it mean? What are you guys trying to do?
What are you guys doing right now?
You're um
Arthur come up man. You're tell me what's what's happening with the latest um
Who's taking a break these days Arthur I need to know we all need to I
Did Arthur I'm so disappointed in you
Oh no, what'd he do?
He's like a fucking
Redditor fucking protector
What? Oh boy who is?
Fucking Arthur, we got we got a fucking dismember him
Crystal fuck. Yeah, we got to get rid of them. We got to get rid of him
You can't be around no more. Nope. Nope. Pettos. No Pettos. No people
Shut up, man, you're not putting a jacket on our no, we don't we don't want none of these people
Don't be doing that man not not to my not to my buddy man not Arthur man
Shut up man Arthur fucking may get on people's nerve, but he's it okay dude man shut up
Look at him. He's making breakfast for his first fiancee. Give me a break. He can't be that bad
Jesus
Saddie seed you need a seed in your pussy or you're in a fucking eyeball, okay?
One up your nose
You need a seed in your nose in your fucking eye bitch
Where there's not a but I think everyone's got got the wrong
Runner dude, maybe it's me that's got the wrong impression of Arthur, but I don't think he's he's a bad dude man
I think he fucks around. He has to take shots. Ivana. I just take shots straight shots
Now you're going at Ivana. Why I don't I don't fucking take no fucking
White claw no more. I don't drink no. I got white claws from fucking months ago from like January and shit
I got beer from Christmas a whole 12 pack and never even open I like Ivana
Don't take shots. I hope you have it in a cool place crystal from Christmas
Well, it's in a gold blaze like it's like Chris if you got beer at Christmas time
It is now May or April. It's nearly May if you've had it sitting out like on the counter
Like in the sunlight or something like that for five months. I was gonna say
No, it's in a bar, okay
No, it's it's not a scene light. No, yeah, I'll be permitted already. Yeah
Hey, did you see that one with the squirrel? It's beer, bitch. Beer, bitch. It's beer, you know, beer goes skunky, right?
You know that. Yeah, that's why it's called skunk.
The squirrels got permitted and they were all falling over.
Fucking hilarious.
We're meeting in fucking a fucking month or two fucking a year or some shit
What did you say you were doing today on Sunday? Didn't we talk about this earlier?
Which it was football season in my son up you and your fucking sports, Jamie
No, that's exactly what it is baby. Oh, it's football season. It is the draft is right around the corner
No, the draft is happening bitch. You're fucking retarded. I just won
Well, you know what I meant like the last few days like the corner was around fuck. You're retarded. I won
I don't care man Stanley Cup playoffs. We'll be starting soon. That's all I don't like it about and I don't even care about that
That would be the only thing I gave a shit about and I don't even know the best fucking. Oh
Ivana, is that you? Oh
Sorry
I'm so sorry. I thought you were even on a birthday. Wait Arthur. What do you mean football?
You mean like American football Australian football or you mean like the international like
No, he hit with the ball
football
Because if you're fucking somebody that I don't really want to hit with a football
I'm really gonna be so bad. It's pretty cool, man. It's called the beautiful game for a reason
Jamie you are Jamie, right? Yeah
Okay, my football is good
Does if you're fucking stupid ass Jennifer, I want to kick you in the fucking head
Yeah
Arthur you have to uh
Shit, I totally forgot what I was gonna say
Arthur what are you making for breakfast for the for the lady Jennifer though
Who's Jennifer? Yeah, I don't know
Who mentioned Jennifer?
Crystal did me. Yeah, but Crystal's insane. We know that I
Don't know who Jennifer is. I don't know who she's talking about Arthur. What are you making for the lady?
It's okay, I'm not gonna get into it, but it's
That fucks dogs
What?
Josh Jin
Josh Jin on video. She's got dog fucking videos. She's a whore. She's like a people are
Just Jin
You know who just Jen is I don't know who that is
Wait, there's there's just Jen there's Jimmy Jen Jen and then there's Jen whatever like that's a total bitch
Which one are you talking about?
Josh all of them
The one that would ski mask
I don't know who that is I don't even know
Sorry, I have to pee
You know, I don't even know who any of these people are
Well, you know
You know the gents, right?
I mean, I don't know the gents again. I just seen them in chat, but you know the gents
No, no
So you don't know Jenny Jen Jen? No, you don't know just Jen
Or the insights chat, I don't know I'm just asking do you know just Jen?
Probably not
Do you know Jen?
What it was a Jen n Gen V? No, Sadie. Why are you saying no? I don't even know where I'm going. Why are you saying no?
Sneets what the hell are sneeze now? What the hell is going on? I have no idea
You guys have all been online for way too long probably too long
Just Jen has the best videos. Yeah, I'm sure Arthur. I think I know what you're talking about
Perfect
Did Arthur Arthur
Did Crystal Marie leave or did you kick her? No, I don't know how to do that up here, you know
I meant I meant like sorry, Jim. Oh
So what's up with you? Why the fuck you watching the football drop? Who gives a shit? I?
Do why?
Because that's what I do
Yeah
Yeah, tonight was basketball
Nick's
Is that you in that picture there? Is that you in the pf? Yeah, Nick's
Nick's and
The other alarms going off hang on a minute
Snips
Who are they playing again? The next it looks like
Don't care I don't care who's playing who
I don't care honestly like I love hockey hockey is my favorite sport and I don't even care who the fucks what's going on there
Timberwolves and nuggets were the other game
Because golden state down here or out of it. I
Still call them Oakland, but they're San Francisco
Where are they now? Where are they located? No Vegas. Let's go
Frisco. Yeah golden state. Oh
Golden state. I was thinking our raiders. We're the raiders now raiders are Las Vegas. They are in Vegas. Okay
Canadians don't like sports. No, I did not we like baseball and hockey
That's about it. Never use that word by the way and lacrosse and curling and curling. Sorry. I forgot about that
Oh, yeah, no, Oakland Athletics were in Oakland and they got moved to Sacramento and they're going to Las Vegas
yeah, I
Won't buy that stadium all the time
Which one the Oakland?
Yep on the way to the Bay. Mm-hmm. I
Remember seeing candlestick when I was a kid when we went out to California. Yeah
Remember driving up from from San Jose. We went up to San Francisco and
Passing by candlestick right there by the water. That was pretty cool. Niners facility is out of San Francisco. Yeah
Mm-hmm where they practice not like I care, but Joe Joe does
but
Shipply is that his name if he cares about the Niners for Kim for Kim. Yeah. Oh, okay. No, he's Ravens AFC. Yeah, I'm just gonna say
Come on Crystal, he'll let you join. I mean football is like I'm sorry, but that's Sundays for me
That's like all day long. I don't I have the red zone. So it's like
Yeah
all the games
I used to, when I was younger, I used to, you know, I used to be into sports.
I would play, obviously, like, when I was young, young, I would play in organized, you know, the house leagues and shit like that.
And then as I got older, I'd play with friends, you know, pick up games, whatever.
I do my own plays, because our coach sucks. And then we don't have a quarterback, so...
I do my own plays.
I have like a...
We do like a football pool too.
What is that?
Do you hear that boomer is a football man?
What? Oh yeah, I can hear it.
It's weird.
That's just my computer. What makes me feel like noise?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure, but...
It's football and basketball.
Wait, I give Paige a little bit of a bad time because wait wait did you hear that music at all wait? No, no music
You didn't hear that
Anyway that grass is meant for football not gold
What music I didn't hear it he was playing some
Alex see Sadie said yeah, yeah, yeah Alex. You're not getting me man
There was some music playing
I didn't hear it and it was getting me hyped up like I actually I was thinking about me Ben's lifting like I don't know
300 pounds or something like that
How much it it you know got me excited?
No, not really
Yeah, Skinwalker Ranch. I knew Paige would like click on that because they can't it's it's different things that happen out there
It's almost like I know about Skinwalker Ranch. I know but I mean
A lot of the stuff is just fucking stories. It's just second-hand
It's second-hand information like none of it's actually proven
And like I honestly I love the stories. I love the stories. I love the stuff
I love supernatural stories and all that shit
But do I actually believe that it's possible? No, you should I don't
People make fun of me and I don't really don't care. I'm not making fun of you. I know people say you I said people
Yeah, yeah, I know people believe different things. I'm just saying I'm
the way I work I'm more of a
You know laws of nature kind of and I know some people don't give that as much
People don't give that as much
Weight as I do, but you know for me it kind of means everything like if it doesn't fall into that then I don't really care
It's not something that we can measure
There goes everything
Hmm
That's cool. See who?
See it looks like me me playing soccer with who though, who's the other not me because I think soccer is fucking stupid, sorry I
Like I like soccer like I mean for the strategy
Hmm, it's it's hard to watch. I agree. It's hard to watch
But I like I like the strategy of it
hmm
It's a long game. It's not one of those games that you look at
Like basketball where things can turn like in five minutes and that shit. It's the it's a long game
Where you look for like 90 minutes?
Which I think is kind of cool
I think it's sort of mental, but when you do this I
Don't think you just how mental I am but now you know
Not really mental but
There's nothing wrong with mentally there like I said in chat earlier. It was it went too far. I'm not mental
I just have depression and that's something that I
Whistle when it finally like showed itself. It was like, oh my god. This guy's freaking out. It's like it's not like I'm fine now
I'm fine
It's just it happens. I
That's the nature of having that shit, you know, and it fucking sucks nothing wrong with it though
What there's nothing wrong with it. Well, there is a lot of things wrong with it. No, I know what you mean
I know what you mean. Yeah, yeah
It sucks to have it, but yeah, I have it. Yeah, I do. Yeah, yeah, I
Have to use it over for everything it sucks
know it please I mean and I'm I'm pretty insightful like I'm pretty I'm quite
self-aware so I kind of like see how things are going and I'm gonna knock it
off what sorry Alex just being Alex again
No, I was gonna say I'm pretty insightful and pretty self-aware of this shit
So, you know, I'm kind of good at writing it out and seeing what's going on and analyzing it and kind of you know working through it
Sometimes yeah, it catches shit. She catches the off guard and it happens
It's unfortunate that it you know it was in public but
Whatever what am I gonna do?
It's like banning people I don't know what's going on who's bad I don't know
So anyways
What's up, Jamie? What else you got to say?
He's mad that I got one many midnight. That's it. Crystal. What? I was just reading her chat
Yeah, Alex, why do you do that?
How does that have a soccer ball?
You can hear the music now, right?
There's no music going.
Shut up. You heard that music, right?
No, just your birds.
Jamie, you're fucking with me.
No.
Yeah, I think you are.
Just the birds.
You can hear my birds. You can hear the birds out my window. Yeah, you hear the birds out my window
But you can't hear fucking music that's being played over our voices. No, I can't hear that. You're totally fucking with me
Never get an Android I have an Android I love it
No, I'm an iPhone. Oh, I got rid of my iPhone. No, I stopped after the idol iPhone 4. Oh
Yeah, I
Don't hear any music. I went to I went to enjoy what?
My god, am I the dentist what the hell was that?
I am tripping, John. I don't know what that was going on.
I didn't hear any music though.
I don't know who did any music though.
Did you just hear that drill?
What?
Fuck off, Jamie.
Drill.
I don't hear any drill.
You're playing with me. You didn't hear that at all.
You mean like a really high-pitched drill like the ones that go on your fucking tooth? Oh, I fucking hate those how they rattle the scar
Yeah, the way that actually that's vibrates it literally and you get bone, you know bone conduction had fun
They literally that the vibration is going to your fucking skull
That's what I'm saying those things going like five thousand seven thousand rpms or something like that man. They were extreme
Vibrates like crazy
Yeah, but the thing about it is that it goes into your fucking skull
That's what makes you out as it goes right into your fucking and it goes in your ear and all that shit
I know I hate that. What's up Jamie's cowboys with your sexy ass accent
What's up hey
Hey is for horses
What's with the jungle noises now
I don't know. Horses don't really go in the jungle.
What?
Horses? Horses don't really go in the jungle.
I said noises. I said jungle noises.
Yeah, I know. That's what I'm saying.
Why, were there horses?
That's what I'm saying.
What the fuck are you saying?
What I just said.
That there's noises.
There are jungle noises? I don't know.
Right, but are they horses?
That's what I'm saying, would I make a fucking sense there to be horses in the jungle?
God damn it, I think Jamie said that there's horse noises.
It doesn't make any fucking sense there to be fucking horses in the jungle.
How could she possibly be in a jungle?
You realize there's nearest jungles in Central America.
Who's in Central America? Oh my god. That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying
Jamie's fucking saying the force is now and you're saying that there's jungles
Happening and I'm saying but everybody's in the in South America, and now I don't know what the hell is happening
Okay, so now I heard a laughter see the weird thing about psyche is that you never know if he's there or if he's
You know talking to his discord friends. So one or the other really are excuse me now. It's not discord
They're they're too high brow for discord
It's Instagram, but it's the same fucking thing
Who's acting manic nomad I am
Oh my god, you think I'm acting manic you haven't seen man. He's acting like a woman
Okay, he's acting like be there when she has hot flashes and she doesn't know
You're acting you're acting like Bita when she's she swears up and down that she doesn't want to fuck me
Lottery
Really had a good laugh track you you had to get the you want to get the iconic laugh track get the laugh tracks from SNL
That was like a shitty lap track.
Yeah, it was like a shitty lap track.
Jamie, can you keep this facade of entertainment going with SIG while I go to the bathroom?
I think that is needs to go do drugs.
Yeah.
Needs to go do drugs.
Oh my God, I never thought I would hear that phrase ever uttered on Earth.
Well, midnight.
You know, all of these things depend on where you place yourself.
This court is different than Instagram so much.
Everything is different depending on how you yourself as an individual do things.
I think the weird thing is that that this court and Instagram at least as people use them are just like hubs for drama.
It's the it's the same thing either way
It's the same thing either way, but but somehow right people's people look down on discord. It's like less
It's low brow
But they're doing the same thing that's the only thing right there they're using these platforms for the
crowd sourcing of negativity
Just put it that way
So it's the same thing
It's the same thing people just thought they think that they're better
I guess they do it on Instagram. They have their little group chats and Instagram and they think that they're better
I think that they're above
Same fucking thing
Jamie, you know, I don't know if you're a part of that. I hate to be calling you out. I'm not
saying this generally
Well, I watch movies in my discord so
I'd like to watch movies at the AMC Village 7.
In.
Fucking New Jersey.
You're going to go there because it was the state.
Yes, I live in New York.
I used to go there.
I used to go there to the AMC Village 7.
Fuck, it's not the village that was that one's in 14th Street.
I used to go to New Jersey, dude, and I used to buy a hell of a big ass bag of weed when
it was legal.
It was legal in New Jersey before it was legal in New York a couple of years ago.
And I would fucking get all smoked out, my friends, so she was funny as fuck.
That's crazy.
We nowadays is so wack, dude, I swear the weed I was smoking then it was like I was
on fentanyl.
I swear, like I was really on like I was like highest fuck real
Hey
I had all of my sex on this score
That wouldn't be sex I've had I've had all of my sex in college
I've had all of my sex in college and everybody wants to pick on me
because of the story that I tell them, but they don't they don't fucking understand.
Like, literally, literally, this bitch
ripped my pants off.
She fucking she pulled my pants down, everything.
I didn't even do anything.
Yeah, girls are kind of uncomfortable. Come on.
Really?
really you think so maybe not to you no I've had some I've had some pretty bad
shit happen to me with girls I'm sorry no no weird I say bad it was just like
Jesus Christ what the fuck are you guys doing midnight nobody's accusing you of
being my girlfriend it's really fucking weird
that I constantly see your message saying that people are accusing you of being my girlfriend.
Nobody is accusing you of being my girlfriend.
It's weird that you keep insisting on that.
It's really strange.
Shout out to you though.
Fucking good morning, I guess.
Are you doing do you hear my birds chirping away? Yes
Fucking things man. Jesus Christ. Are they your birds? Are they on the street? No, they're mother nature's birds
People have accused you of being war kitty Rose. I'm not lying. Okay. They did that once like what years ago
And you're still like clinging on to it. Like at some point it just seems like you're clinging on to like hope
Really weird. Are you clinging on to some kind of hope?
Cuz I've literally never heard anyone say that before maybe they said it once
That's just weird. It's very very strange
very strange
I don't really care what you say cuz clearly you got fucking screws loose. All right
Birds is there any way like where the fuck is this this gay guy? Where's this gay guy at who me?
That's the joke that you're gay you came out of the closet I suppose
Okay, well congratulations. Yeah, you know muzzle tov. I think is the appropriate thing to say
No, the Jews hate gaze
Seems that everyone's not it. That's not a joke. I don't know why you're laughing
I don't think you need to fucking assign one maybe people maybe maybe gaze should be hated
No, man, I just saw your, your, uh, comment, maybe it is a sign of low tea. Maybe I've
been saying that for the longest about this guy, he should get his levels checked. I know
I guess he gets all pissy every time I say it, but like, yo, I don't get pissy when you
No, man, I'm never worse than beta you've got you've got the same
Good thing, how you doing? I get all pissy in
Are you a tell Steve? Are you on your period Jamie? Go back to being silent and not saying anything. Thank you
Oh, why are you hiding tonight? Come on. Don't hide midnight like come on
I mean, I feel bad for Jamie. She's just she's just a little shy. She's just a little shy. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Hey psyche come up here real quick, bro
I gotta ask you something
Psyche
You don't want to face me or what
This is a question bro like I'm not upset, but why would you fucking ban me from your chat, bro?
I
Sound like Sam and
You're upset though
Are you saying you're saying that you don't want to sound like you're upset, but you do sound like you're upset
No, I'm not upset, but it's just weird like out of nowhere, bro. Like, you know me
But why is this of any concern to you? I expect this sort of homosexual behavior from so I mean a gay man
I mean sick you cry about a lot of shit
So I'm not crying about a gay guy acting like a woman you happy for
No, I'm not
No, I'm not no you happy for nope
I have never cried about a homosexual man acting like a woman clumsy clumsy what I do is I tell you
That's what they're doing. I don't cry you're not banned try typing
Okay
Oh, now mom man. Thank you psyche. Wow rogue nomad rogue nomad
I don't have hypogonadism for my 20s. I've actually had I was a teenager. I don't
Secondary secondary hypogonadism since I was a teenager so I was very young
It's not something that has occurred just now. It's been a long term
long term
Who knows who knows rogue nomads. Maybe if I had no more testosterone levels, I would look like you
Who knows? I mean, I don't know
Clearly you have to get to some sort of uh, you're you take something
Like come on, dude
Don't lie to my face and tell me that you don't take nothing to look the way that you do because I know that that's not true
Are you done talking about another way?
So, I don't know. Maybe if I took tremolo and I would also look like that
Uh, I know for a fact that that stuff, when you take it, it doesn't take much effort to look that way,
especially if you take creatine and you have a lot of liquid retention in your muscles.
There's variables to this. There's variables to this.
What do we got to get on everybody? Why do we have to fucking hit on everybody's weaknesses or perceived weaknesses? Why? Why?
I'm not hitting on anyone's perceived weakness. That's actually a strength.
I mean all this is exactly what you're describing is a strength
What is it's not a weakness it's a strength cx
For sexual what are you talking about my ears? I can't handle sexual talk. Um, it's strength
I'm just saying why why shout out to Jamie's cowboys. She couldn't take the heat so she had to leave the kitchen
Why are we tearing each other down then?
I'm not tearing him down, man.
God bless him.
The guy wants to take tremble on God bless you, man.
You want to take tremble on and get all ripped?
God bless you.
More power to you, buddy.
But don't fucking act like you're better than me
because you're fucking medicated while you don't take the whole
and act like you're better than me.
Don't act like you're something special
because you're taking drugs that enhance your body.
100 fold than it could ever be naturally I fucking that's that's all it is. That's all it is
That's all it is. That's not tearing someone down
Bro, stop taking those hormone pills for real. I
Take estrogen pills. What do you do? I know you do you take pills that make you a straight man?
No, you take pills that make you a gay man
Why would you need a pill to make you gay or straight?
Look up what it means when gay guys go to the gay bar
Look up what it means when you go to the gay bar and you have rooms stuck up your ass
acid
Goddamn clumsy. How was your night, man?
It's been cool, man. It's been chilling, you know
But psyche nothing against you, bro. I was just curious, man. I thought maybe maybe I said something that rubbed you wrong, but
That's why I tell you
Psyche this guy got rubbed by a broomstick the wrong way
He did not want to get rubbed by the broomstick the long way
Sigg is an expert in all topics that I've ever existed. No rogue nomad. It's called being able to roll with the punches
That's what it's called. All right
Just because you're a fucking big dude doesn't mean that you know how to do that. All right
I've always said I don't think you're you're an idiot. I never thought that I always thought you have good
Annunciation which which tends to lean towards what I think about clumsy
These guys are fucking twice my age and they don't seem to carry that wisdom over
I would think you have two times my wisdom
I would think that you understand things two times better than I do
I would think that you would make two times in the sense that I
Yet to see that
Why do you have got going for yourself right now? Who do you live with do you own your own spot?
Do you pay your nope? No take care of their nope. Hell. No. Hell. No grow up grow up
No, no before before you sit there and talk about I have my family paying everything for me. Yep. I know you do
I know you do see again be grateful for that
Hi, psyche
For that
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. Oh
Okay, so things it leaves immediately
Let me answer your question a little bit more precisely clumsy if I had
something going for myself hypothetically of course why the fuck do you
think I would be telling you about it?
SIG to stop.
Do you tell me about your livelihood clumsy? Let me ask you a question clumsy
was your livelihood what pays your bills?
What is your skill? What is your trade? What is your value that makes you money? Tell me about yours. I
Don't need to say all you're not gonna tell me
Why is it that you don't want to tell me that?
Other that's a rhetorical question. No, it's further. The question is why is it that you expect me to answer that question for you?
When you don't want to answer that question for yourself, can I talk now?
It's better in what a universe and what form of logic. Do you expect me to answer that question for you?
I know when you're done, bro. While you stay silent and not answer that question yourself
Okay, in what world does that make any sense?
Because it don't make sense in this one. Okay, let me know when you're done talking. Okay
Okay, let me know when you're actually gonna give an answer. Are you done?
Oh wait, I know you're not gonna give an answer because you're a stupid-ass retard
Are you are you done?
Sick, I don't need to explain all that all I have to say is
I got a lot of shit to show for
That's all I have to say. What do you have to show for big besides running your mouth?
That's all I gotta say
I don't know
No, I think psyche put in the back so I could be able to talk because I don't be using to shut the fuck up
But I'm just being honest like I'm not no better than anyone but in in all reality like he
Downs everyone because of certain things
But look at yourself, bro. Like I'm just being honest. I know that comes up comes up harsh, but
I could be more of an asshole, you know what I'm saying, but I'm trying to be somewhat reasonable with him
So he could kind of understand but he's still young
Everyone got their own
You know, not everyone's the same
Zendik galaxy fold
Is that the galaxy fold? No, it's the uh, what is it? Damn? He got the galaxy fold smartphone
And it's the s25
It's the galaxy fold. No, it's not the fold. Shut up. I'm telling you the 26 just came out. What are you talking about?
25 was last year
We might be the 25 26. I don't know whatever
I'm not going to lie, dude.
I got the fucking Galaxy Fold 7.
I got the fold seven.
They're a question. How are you?
Hi, Jim. Oh, Aaron's here.
Hi. What's up? What's up, Aaron?
How are you doing?
Be nice to Aaron.
How are you doing, Aaron?
I'm being nice. Hello.
It's so nice to see you. Hello.
Oh, my God.
Aaron, I miss you. How are you?
I miss you, too, honey.
I'm good. I'm working on a new blanket. Yay. Yay. Are you watching the draft? Huh? Are you watching the NFL draft? No. I'm going to be surprised. I'm done watching the draft.
NSC. Hey, Clumsy. You're with Dallas, remember?
And yes thing, I said hi to you before you turn around later.
Hey, Clumsy, Katie, you're here earlier.
Oh, is she? How's she doing? Is she doing good?
She's doing good. She was helpful.
What's up, Sean? James? Are you riding motorcycles?
So you're a tough guy?
I bet I would ride your motorcycle faster than you, faggot.
Hey, Lee.
Oh, I'm riding a motorcycle.
Yeah, I was so disappointed in football that I just gave up like halfway through. Don't give up
Don't give up. Just come to the NFC UBI. I have a lot of work. I am NFC.
Yeah, he's gonna give up the bears and go with Dallas.
I was gonna I was gonna ask you
Keep playing on my fear of clowns man. I have no idea. You know my clowns thing
I don't I don't have a fear of them. No, I don't like clowns either, but I like it and I like what is it?
Clowns in the cornfield. It's a murder. I mean I scare crawls. Yeah, I like horror. So it's like, you know, like horse
Holy shit, I can't wait for the next one. Yeah. Yeah, fuck. Yeah, I love shit like that
This this guy here actually James. I'm not gonna crash my motorcycle. I'm gonna crash your motorcycle son James
What do you mean? You're gonna crash your motorcycle. I'm not gonna crash my motorcycle. Thank you. I'm crashing your shit. Fuck you mean
It's like you're gonna face those. How are you? Oh, yeah. No, he's letting people on and off and I was like Aaron's up there
I gotta go
He was up here earlier
Aaron, how you doing? Did you did you even say hello to me? I did and you turned around and walked away
This Nick is all sorry
That must have been when my dog was this guy bought an R1 as a starter motorcyclist
I'm gonna start off with it
You must start off with an R1, and then I'm going to get an H2R.
That was his mindset.
He said, what are you doing right now?
What are you doing right now?
They'll be talking about that out to rogue tremble on CC. What are you doing right now?
Do you understand? He's a chat. He takes tremble on right like you understand why right yo
I wonder I wonder what this guy wrote nomad would look like if he was not
Super physiologically enhanced by drugs. I wonder
Go tell him these niggas, bro. I feel bad for these niggas, bro
These niggas have to take drugs to feel bad or nigga. I don't need drugs your niggas need drugs
Talking but you can waste it every fucking day and show your
that's not drugs, that's not drugs, I buy it from the store
I buy it from the store that government says you have this
so now it's not a matter of following the law, is that what it is?
yep, yep, I'm a law-abiding United States citizen
just like you're a law-abiding Canadian, United States Canadian citizen
For the most part, sure, but not everything. So that's what I'm talking about.
Let me ask you a question. You think I'm going to be snitching on myself about me smoking
meth? Nick, I'm not ever going to snitch on myself, nigga. So what? I'll be smoking meth.
You niggas be smoking meth and you guys get all scared, nigga. You guys start talking to the
Hey, sometimes the malls have really good ideas sick. Yeah, they got better better personality than most
You guys be getting scared when you smoke meth
I've never smoked. I'll cause not a drug. I go to the store and buy it. I would never smoke meth in my life, man
So then you just eat Adderall, so then you just
Adderall in my life. So you just true
Concertive I vans. I've never true that you don't like I've never had it in my life
So you chewed a Tylenol pill and you didn't know what it was even though you knew the purpose
Was fake
Medications you're gonna get on you chewed the part and you knew it was fake
I mean you chewed the perk knowing that it was fake. Oh, I've had perk knowing that it was actual perk. I liked it
Yeah, yeah, yeah full chewed that shoe
You chewed that shit after buying it from the homeless guy in front of his fuck your apartment
So you're fucking kidding this is Canada we get it from the pharmacy. He walked into his
Apartment building. He's like, yo, let me get a pack right now
and he's thinking that you're going to sell it, but you're just going to snort that shit up your nose that whole night
I've only ever snorted coke
Sorry, sorry, sorry, I started mescaline too once
That's gay, no wonder you're such a homosexual, it explains a lot
Right
so even clubs you are both on the same brainwave that's what it is
Yeah, that's it ding I was gonna ask you. Yeah, you're starting drugs that are like
legal over there like I'm I think like heroin and stuff like that or you know, I mean
No, I might be some he wants to move where they're treating something with with with these things that it might be legal in that sense
But in general, are you telling me that they don't have methadone clinics in Texas?
Just weed weed is illegal now. That's all. Well, I'm see they don't have methadone clinics in Texas
No, they don't
All right, see that's how I know that you're really in Texas because everyone in Texas is fucking retarded as fuck
That's where my family that's where my family came through when they went over the border they came through El Paso
And then they were like fuck this shit
Did they cross legally?
Hell yeah
The reason I asked that thing because I remember seeing uh some kind of like
I don't know if it was a documentary or something like that, but they were like treating
The people that were trying to get off of stuff and I guess they were treating them with uh smaller doses of
heroin and
I was like, it could be clumsy. Like I said, there might be some special, uh, programs where that stuff is allowed. Like we are a little, you know, liberal, a little more progressive in those kinds of things, but in general, no, it's not legalized. Like you can't just go by.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All my family, United States citizens, W, shout out to Mad Hatton.
Smash is cool.
Yes, all of my all of my family is United States citizens. Just like
Just like the United States Parliament House
You hear me smash is like an older retarded me even though he's younger than me and oh wow
He's definitely more retarded than Aaron
But he heard you I'm an ice man
Wait, who was it Leo? I'm a mega man. I'm a mega man
huh
smart rip take a
Rest in peace take a
We're a psyche
He's in the back. He's playing with his asshole. He's masturbating right now
He's listening to us talk while he's playing with a vibrator in his asshole because he's a
God bless him, you know what I mean? It's a free country. This guy wants to be gay. He's in California where all the people be at
Aaron how you doing Jamie
That's good. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah
That's good. That goes quick to change. God damn it telling Aaron. That was Leo
He wasn't doing very good and he heard you smoke mega man
Then who wasn't doing good psych
No, Leo Leo Maine Coon
Leo is the Maine Coon wasn't doing good. Yeah, Mike
Who's yellow the main cool? Yeah, I mean this is fascinating
His name is Leo. Oh
On the same page Jamie, huh? I think we got on the same page knowing who
Leo is what Leo is. I think they got it now. I think they well clumsy does yeah
I want to mean cool. I'm not gonna lie like those cats are so fucking beautiful. Yeah
Yeah, so he's starting to come around up smash you ain't gonna fucking man nobody at trivia
I can't see the chat from here. This is it if I see the chat it tells me I have to
What is it like and then I have to connect to YouTube and I know I'll kick myself
So I'm on the site. Oh, no, why are you banding broom? Come on. Yeah, it's it's it's kind of like weird
I I've had that done to me
On my old phone like where it would do that. That's why I had to download the fucking app
But it seemed like when I download the app
One thing cleared up, but another thing happened. You know what I mean? Like so if I do that clumsy
Will it kick me off of here because I don't know
Unless you have a second device
Oh shoot. I would use in my computer to write people in the chat, but listen. I'm not very coordinated. So yeah
If you want to stay on the show be back in three minutes, I'm gonna play a song
Thank you so much. Is he talking to me?
Yeah, go back to me.
I'm fire everybody gotta take names in the air like a trial I didn't make banning out pick a side prove
You're one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust. I said, I don't know the story
I'm a sign enough on claims you want instant verdicts. I don't play those games
No paper then I'm asking for more that defense. That's me checking the floor
But I'm supposed to be, you were back in me
Building me, like in the show
Till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You want control, dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standard
No, he's trying to speak over me, but this is mine
Not your community
Turns to a pile on waves, same voices yelling different names on the stage
Everyone knows, yeah, everyone says, but nobody stops to question the threads
Proof in the DMs I didn't review, or proof you decided was already true
You want me to act on a crowd-made case, then punish me when I don't keep pace
Man, a few people now I'm afraid
Oh, maybe I'm done with the games you play, you push iCold and call it
Like in the show, till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
If you want control, dress up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not your community
I made you judge, jury, and now executioner live in my chat
Nah, I'm not Bill Light
To keep you agreeing with me
You drew your lines and I didn't chase it
You called and lost, I replaced it
Now it's me standing where I choose to be
Yeah, this is mine
Not your community
I've got to figure that out another day how to download that.
This ain't your community.
Get out of here.
Hi.
Why would I be mad?
Hang on, Sean.
Oh, Mod.
I'm sorry, Mod.
Never mind. Okay, you're annoying
Bitch
No one this shit, I think
Think I'm done with this shit. What'd they do?
What didn't they do and uh, yeah
I'm still trying to figure out how to hook up the so I could join the chat and talk like I
Hmm. I want to sit here and bitch at me all night and all the chat likes to talk shit about me everywhere, huh?
Yeah, I fucking like let up here fucking all night
Why, why are you banning me? Why are you banning me?
You fucking budget assholes.
What about that?
I miss Erin.
Maybe I am self-stabbing out of myself, RG.
I'm singing this fucking bullshit.
Stalker?
Jan. Hi. I could barely see on my phone. Shamrock.
I can see.
Does anyone want to tell me what to do?
Does anyone tell B to what to do?
Does anyone tell statement what to do? No.
Just tell Psyche what to do.
Just give Psyche about the shit.
Everyone is laughing at Psyche, right?
Did I miss something while I was trying to download that app?
Oh, no, it was a song. That was just a good song.
I'm trying to figure out.
Look, I have Crystal Marie up here
screaming about she's gonna sue me for my codex.
Because there was a quote about,
some quote that she probably did fucking say.
She has she says weird shit like that
Coming out of nowhere. I mean geez
Hmm oh
Jamie it was quite a ride though, but I think I'm ready to move on
Okay, I came here with love actually. Well, oh now I can see
I can feel that ever since you had me download that app. It's all confusing. Okay
Jen
Yes
Hi
Ask me jen. Hi jen
Hi, jamey. How are you? I'm good
I'm laying I'm laying in a bed full of pussy right now
Oh my god, that sounds fun
All my cat all my cats are in here. Oh
Yeah, they're pussy cats, but they're boys
They're having a lesbian experience. No, I'm not definitely not a lesbian. I'm not into any of that stuff. I am
Yeah, and you know what? That's great for you and that's awesome. I celebrate that for you, but I am a Krusty cracker conservative.
Okay, so what do you think, guys? What do you think should happen to gay people?
I don't think anything should happen to gay people. I think, I think.
people should just be left alone.
Thanks.
I agree with that, I agree with that.
I think you should just,
I think people should just leave each other alone
and they can find the people that they belong with
and they can do whatever they want to do.
Are you a chicken lady?
Is this Jen?
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay, okay, okay.
I knew Ziggy is,
but you're different than the chicken army lady.
Are you the same or the different?
Yeah, it's it's me, but
Ziggy and I aren't together anymore, so oh, yeah
Yes, yeah, I'm right. What was it like dating the leasing of a good Charlotte?
It was it was like it's like being tortured every day with the reward
It's like a BDSM relationship only there. There's there's no loving partner on the other side
The hell and this well, are you doing well? There we go warning folks or gee hello
Is psyche here or did he bounce? Yeah? Yeah, he's around. Yeah, I'm rock. I know why are you so angry with me?
I
Opposition are you you're very direct so he takes that he takes that to heart
So I'm being told what to do by Tony. He's telling me he's telling me you don't run your show
I run your show or we run your show or whatever read all the black people from jail
Fuck out and then it's like and then it's like everyone feels so comfortable saying oh
You know, oh you you hit your cats your cats are your props you starve your cats you abused your cats
I just mentioned someone might have had kids.
I didn't even know if she does or not.
And then it's like, oh, you mentioned I have kids.
Oh, I didn't say anything about them.
It was fucking the other guy said a comment.
I told him not to say anything.
If you're angry that I said you should apologize to Kate.
Right, I don't know or fucking apologize.
You should apologize for making me a fucking donkey.
But she's like, explain it.
Right, explain it then.
Don't hide him.
Explain it.
Can you please unblock me and Jack,
because that's pretty fucking ridiculous.
I didn't do anything.
okay well i mean it's like yeah i mean i usually like clumsy up with the car
really upset because i said you seem to still sabotage i don't know he wants to make fun of
that's what what what's what's mine in the back bro yeah why why because it's my show i get to
decide who's back at it we gotta get you like he's like he's fucking dick i heard the song
I was fucking Sam and shut up
Yeah, we heard it we get it, you know, ain't see ain't see music you got the shake
Come on man, oh you shut up. I mean the guys what why are you telling me to run my show? I don't understand
I don't understand that was just talking for me for about about me for hours in fucking
I'm what's her name is chat in case you oh you know oh it's like he does this and that
means it's like Jesus try a fan by Sam and you're gone die okay you know I don't owe
you a place on my show okay get out of here
What I don't know what to say what we're getting Jesus corn. What?
It seems like it's a walker. I don't hear a fishy voice. I
Agree with you about that one
That's a catchy song. I mean, it's a knee slapper. Okay. Yeah, you put a lot of emotion into it. You could tell you could tell
It's my community
I'll do what I want to do with it. It's my prerogative. Oh, wait a minute. You ripped that off
Yeah, you're a you use AI does this okay? I get it. I get it
With your AI you fucking bitch, what do you do with me use it out?
Yes, I'm from a noose with his AI and he's making fun of my fucking fuck yourself. I wrote that
That's cool
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
like, you can do what you want.
You can do what you want.
Thank you.
Someone got to get there.
You don't have to listen.
They're all just.
Someone gets it.
It's my show.
They're all just, that's part of the game.
That's part of the game.
I don't like it.
I don't, it's not like any game
that they make up the rules.
That's fine.
It's not a game.
I didn't mean to say.
You don't have to like the game.
Flip that motherfucking board over.
Yeah I am. And strut around like you won anyway. Who gives this shit? I did win! Psyche always wins! Psyche always wins! Woo!
Hey.
I'm still here.
I wish Paige would kick back too.
Exactly.
Paige got called a whore by, you know, by Crystal Murray,
so I think she's not.
What?
Who called you a whore?
I know.
Crystal Murray.
Crystal Murray is saying all kinds of shit, yeah.
Oh, Crystal Murray is just that's like, man,
Crystal Murray is the human equivalent of putting
a Mentos into a Diet Coca-Cola.
Think about it
Fizz that goes everywhere and ends up on your you can fucking make a river flowed out of her ear wax
Yeah, don't worry about that bitch. I've never the first time I met that bitch
She said all kinds of things to me. She thought I was somebody. I don't know who she thought I was
But you are somebody with jammed chicken lady to me about fucking told me to fuck my dead mother
Oh my god live. I don't I don't even know
Just angry just anger and violence a lot of these people I think have parental issues
right
Yeah, you want a flirt, okay
Yeah, are you single I can't believe you did that you actually took that one. Okay. All right
Oh, I think you found it. I think you found it. Yeah, Jan
Clips is really need of a woman. What I I am. Yeah, I'm not gonna
I am single, but I am available. I
I'm casting a wide net, you know, I don't know who who gets caught in it. I'm not you know
no one
No one take it personally
I was kidding about the flirting thing, man. I just didn't want to be sitting in the back anymore. Well, you want to do a mass-on ban, please so I could type
Like a child
Come
I mean, we're all we're all fucking nutbags. We're all mad here. Yes, you're all nuts. Alice in Wonderland, dude
What's down is up. What's up is right? What's sideways is left and it's all it's all a
It's all madness.
Well, I'm not a white rabbit here.
I'm drinking my adrenochromy, motherfuckers.
Stay away from my brain.
I'm done.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got a little bit.
YouTube is the equivalent of like one of those Dolly
posts that, you know, Salvador Dolly posters.
Right.
I used to have the Toria door in my life.
Slight and slowly down.
It's like Alison Wonderland without the fun and the drugs.
No, nobody likes my analogy.
I like it.
Oh, it's Salvador Dali.
I had the melting bowl and stuff like that.
I had the Toria bowl.
I can't hear anybody.
Can't hear me?
Oh, she's got to download that app.
Oh, hey.
I'm back.
Are you going to listen to me again?
Am I gonna what you're gonna keep bitching I have a download an app bitching at you
What the fuck can fuck your mama? I can't hear any but I can hear you I ain't with the drama
I hate you know what happens is when you when somebody leaves
It'll
Hear so when you have to go through this you know, it's like the app for StreamYard
It's for an iPhone. Are you gonna iPhone?
damn it. Yes, I am. That's what happens. Last time was like. Can you not hear me? Uh-uh.
She can't hear me? She can't. I'm trying to take, I'm trying to walk her through those
steps how to do it. All right, okay. She can only hear me. So I can say all kinds of disgusting
things right now and she wouldn't care. Yeah, but that's not. I would definitely care.
I definitely would. I can hear you now, but I can't hear Jamie. Oh, no. Okay. All right. Yeah
Okay
Damn it. Why do I have to download an app on the iPhone?
Right is it stream yard?
It's like the world the hate
Yeah, we with the iPhone users. Yeah, apparently you gotta use the stream yard app. Yeah, you have to be so different
Really different bullshit
And I don't mean not in like the psyche is gay way. I mean gay is an offensive way
Do you want to tell her how to do it or that's I'm not do I want to tell her how to do it. Yeah, it's the stream yard app
Yeah, I'm on it's a stream yard up
Okay, yeah
Totally different. So what I just go to what Google now play no you go to the stream yard out and then
connect it
And then what yeah, I know Jamie go on so after she gets the stream yard app
Yeah, it'll take you through all that
It'll take you through all that Jen
Download the stream yard app, and it'll take me through all that stuff. Yes
I imagine you're probably gonna have to sign in with some kind of email account, right?
Yeah, I was gonna know like you
Mind you too
It's a good thing my password is the same for everything.
Okay, so you should be all right.
Prompt 2024, that's my password for everything.
Are you insane?
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Shut up, I know both of you.
What is, why am I in this bloody community?
All you fucking conservatives.
I'm doing good.
Don't get me started, I'm doing good.
No.
Because conservatives are the best.
That's why.
fucking idiot. Come on. Conservatives have the best kinks. Not you. I said he was a brain
and we keep him at home where they belong. That's right.
When I say I'm a liberal you guys go fucking nuts, right? Because you guys you guys have some
You guys have some kind of image of liberals, which are all the like the blue-haired
I'm sure I'm sure some people do I'm sure some people do but that's not true. I don't have
Liberals can be they can have whatever color hair they want. I used to have pink hair. It's okay
I mean the color of the hair wasn't the key thing. I was just saying you guys see you guys see the
You guys see the far left as liberal
No, no, no, no, I have a I have a I have a very libertarian
friend and
Yeah, no, I don't I can't say that's true for everybody because yeah when
you know when Fox News is talking about the
Liberals the general, you know, ever what brings to mind is yet the far left
Yeah, that's our bra. I know everybody's not like that. Well, I know Jamie knows Jan
I don't know if you know, I'm a Canadian and I generally vote liberal up here
Yep, okay, so so what does that mean?
That's liberal
No, I'm just messing around. No, because I'm just great. Let's see y'all are our neighbors
Because you guys think we're all we're communists and all that shit up here like I am not far left in in any way
I'm like center left. I I'm I'm okay with
with social programs
That's basically it that that's the only thing that distinguishes me from left and right
Okay, so hey, and that's and that's fine, you know, it's it's the same thing the same thing here with America anybody who
Who looks at an entire country and says well, that's a whole country of liberals is?
Dumb because it's just like in the United States just like in any country
You're gonna have people that are conservative leaning you're gonna have people that are taking more liberal worldview
You're gonna have people that are right in the middle
You gonna have people
It's the government.
They classify the country, you know, if it's got a, if it's got a liberal government that
classifies the country or a far left, you know, shit, but, but it's, it's still comprised
of, of individuals that are capable of their own thought and drawing their own conclusions.
Y'all aren't just a bunch of lemmings.
How about six dollars?
Yeah.
You're capable of your own thought.
You can vote conservative.
You can vote liberal.
Whatever.
Sure.
Do you it's just like here
What's a genie? What are you saying? It's a dollar gas. Would you be upset about that everyone?
What you guys only you guys say?
Canada yeah, yeah, yeah, I do I do say it a lot
So I do I don't notice it, but people have mentioned it to me. Yeah, I guess
Definitely sound Canadian, you know, he he took our refineries. You know what?
I've traveled a lot and some of the nicest people I've ever met were in Canada. I
Gotta say when I travel overseas and I meet up with Americans
The first thing they always want to do is denounce the current president doesn't matter who it is
In order for them to get along with the people that they're traveling with they need to denounce the current president
Well, you'll never get that for me. I'm just saying that's how it's been. I've been traveling like I
You know, whatever. I've been a single person pretty much my whole life. I've been traveling like my whole life
I've gone to places. I've met lots of Americans overseas. Oh, wow. No. Oh
Sorry Jan I was I was gonna do another hour if someone would have donated a dollar at least but no one donated even a dollar
And I've been here for five hours. I'm not my monetized channel right now
Everyone was sitting up here all night. I let everyone say their shit
And so no one said so I'll just play music for the rest of the night and so someone in this one's in the next hour
When I'm playing music once they do a donation and then I'll consider starting the panel again, but thank you for coming Jan
I appreciate it. Okay. Thanks. Thanks. Thanks Mike
I love you. Okay, I'll come back soon, okay?
Sorry about that. Okay, bye.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-du
I was already waiting in the margins of your pain
Psyche's nightmares come alive
Where the beautiful things go to survive
You bring the darkness, I bring the light
We burn together at the edge of night
We built a room of mirrors, for the luminous design
When their views dry up, gotta hate the one crooked, gotta sermon half-baked
Say, I'm praying for you while these screenshots get saved
They got concerned and their boys poison in the cup
Say, I hate drama while they wind it up, got pearls in a death grip clutch
It's better when they're smiling
No horns, no pitchfork, no open hay
Just five squishes and a coupon for betrayal
Da-dina-na, da-dina-na, da-dina-na, da-dina-na
When the mess appears, always so shocked with crocodile tears
and sell the stain. Danger two, they split the crew. Make folks doubt what they already knew.
Danger three, they bait reaction, then point and scream. Look bad attraction, oh sweetheart,
you built amaze. Now you're acting scared of the fire you raised.
So if they rush like Destiny's clone
The roll case closed on a buddy troll
Whisper networks
And concern little bystanders
Welcome
Please keep your rumors folded neatly under your chairs
We'll be using them as confetti
They whispered he's dramatic, unstable, hard to please
Then clutched their pearls so tightly, they near cut off their own breeze
A private little worry here, a solemn little sigh
A bless his heart, I'm nervous with a sparkly alibi
They never tell a whopper when a half-truth will suffice
They serve it room and temperature and call the plating nice
They let the room assemble it, they let the crowd infer
They stand there looking in a sentin' beige and cashmere fur
But I know this production, I know each tacky prop
The script, the cue, the fake concern, the tasteful little slop
You wanted me to burst on stage and shriek till I was horse instead
You studied all my buttons like a butler studies wine
You thought my nerves were vending slots that paid out on your time
A jab a glance, a poison joke, a friend with updates twice
Impressed and pressed and pressed and hoped I'd melt for your device
But then I turned to marble with a very decent tan
No jaw clench, no heavy sigh, no let me clear this fam
You searched my face for weakness like a coupon in a drawer
Found nothing but good posture and a gaze that said bored
kitten heels you curator of spin you cannot run a puppet show and no one
yanks within a mastermind a grand machine a dark strategic horde no just
one sweaty socialize
Then came my favorite counterspell, strategic visibility
No frantic notes, no courtroom speech, no opera of fragility
I simply kept on showing up, composed and very real
Which is for those who traffic lies, a deeply rude ordeal
I smiled at folks, did solid work, behaved with normal grace
And every calm interaction, slapped confusion in your face
Because the portrait that you painted wild, unwell absurd
Look flimsy next to me, just being warm and well-groomed and heard
Then one by one, without a fuss, I spoke to people plain
Not here's my case, not choose a side, not let me name your stain
Just human voice, direct eye contact, ordinary air
And funny how a planted thought
On suggestion, fog and vibe
A tiny cult of secondhand impressions in a tribe
But lies are cheap upholstery, they spe-
bent and cornered by your art. But all you did was train my eye and sharpen every part.
You meant to make me smaller, anxious, broken, underscored. Instead you made me elegant and not
Thank you darlings. Take your bartend.
Distrust the neutral one.
Check, check.
Same search.
Freshers smoke you don't bring facts you bring light, and you don't tell truth you cast rolls, and you pick
You build a case out of
Side eyes thumbnails and tone turn a rumor to a rally put it up on the throne
Take a dozen loose fragments stitch a monster from scraps then your point of your creation like see I'm just stating facts
With suggestion, let implication do flips Got a mouth full of poise
Take deep, bad faith, crack, day-long
First comes the grand theory, then the cask gets assigned
Then you act like you got X-ray vision, straight into my mind
Everybody's a puppet, everybody's in play
Till the facts hit the room and your mystique melts away
You call paranoia wisdom, call projection again
How you do it right float a charge then dim the light let the audience connect the dots while you act shocked at what they got
I'm just asking question sure with a loaded wink and a poison slur. I'm just noticing a trend. Yeah, every witch hunts is that in the end
With a story on your tongue
Talking like a judge done ruled before the trials even begun
You got sparks but no fire
Got smoke but no flame
Just a trailer full of gossip with my picture on the frame
You take a half truth to the tavern
Let it soak all night and gin
Sunshine and somebody's need for fame
You can dress it up in glory, you can make it sound grand
But guys are paying gospel just because it's loud and plain
No, you ain't breakin' me, you're just puttin' on the show
At the rumor, rodeo
Yeah, you can keep on ridin' circles in your own satchel
I won't be your clown tonight
Thank you for watching, see you next time!
Since the silence weren't proud
You thought it was connection
Just a table just a seat
But the floor beneath you shifted you would never
Never say yes a master class in distance dressed up as finesse invitations drift past like ghosts in the hall
You're not excluded. Just not counted at all. They study your rhythm catalog your tone and mirror it back like it was always their
Owners optimization while they tighten the thread. You're speaking your truth
So you learn the quiet rules they never explain Don't show every car, don't echo their name
Something else his hands on the wheel
stream signing all your thoughts, smiling in the mirror while your real self rots
polite little prisoner trained to obey, you call it being good but you're decaying that way
you swallow every instinct, fire your teeth down smooth, call it self control but you just
removed your proof you had claws, you had fire, you had something divine, now you apologize for
crossing your own line, call John whispered from the grave, make the dark conscious so it digs
your cave but you muted the message saying
Perfect even you forgot polished every angle to your soul got caught. They don't love you
They love the road you placed an innovation for a ghost in the display
Laugh on command now. Don't you ever yes you fake is a fracture
That's your buried ground, laziness, that's burnout drown
Jealousy maps where your hunger lives, rate shows what your silence gives
Your enemies are blueprints in disguise
Read them right, you weaponized
your wild got tamed, your fire got labeled too much, too fast, now get dimming your-
Like they're sitting across Negotiate storms instead of taking the loss
That voice in your chest isn't random or fade, it's a signal
starts bending.
Shout out to the Cash App.
I'll be right back, okay?
One more song, and I'll come back on the stream, okay?
Shout out to the $20 Cash App, thank you so much.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
in the guy that I was falling in love in the summer time, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, in a
unify, in a unify, feeling oh so unify, in a la-
c'est kiff
I'm alone now
Fantasies place my skull like alkalites in a corridor
I keep seeing you as the perfect kind
Not because you were real, but because my hunger can paint halos on emptiness
I almost had you, or I almost had the idea of you
But it wasn't time, so I swallowed the lessons we never got to learn
And I practiced not thinking about how easily I would've loved you
If the universe had opened the door an inch wider
I miss you, then I never met you
I'm a loner, I'm a loner now
Then it's okay to cry
They said I was selfish
But all I did was carry you like a secret script
She told me I was selfish
When I'm the one bleeding the loss
Sometimes I interrogate myself
Sometimes the blood in my head turns into sermons
If I'm such a creator
Why can't I make you?
Why can't I conjure you?
How do I breathe the need and she abuses me?
I miss you
And I'll never met you
I'll let you home alone alone
I'll sing you to sleep every night in the tent
My shield, Scorpio's empire rising
My destiny rising
Crystal. What did you do when I was gone, Crystal? Crystal, girl.
I know. There is a blessing with not giving a fuck anymore. It really does come a blessing with it.
I'm not going to do my Michael Jackson because he man already said Michael Jackson
crotch grab was already oh it's getting old oh someone tells him it's funny and then he was doing
well it's called it's called stand-up comedy it's like you know you do things for different
audiences you're not if you're always there at my show and you're gonna see my same jokes over
I mean, it's like, people don't get it though.
They're like, oh my God, okay, he sucks.
They watch every show.
Yeah, Chrisley might, Chrisley, you call Paige a whore.
She's not, like not at all.
Like that's like, she's like the furthest thing
from one that she might, okay, here's what Paige is.
Paige might be a lot of things.
She's not a whore, she is this.
She is actually a dolphin.
a lot of sound effects. Wow. Okay. Shout out to the $20 cash app. Thank you for
stupid. Yeah, you did. Oh, I have it on. Oh, Crystal, you've been clipped. It's going to go
on your quote, quote page in the codex for sure. It's going to say crystal to page,
you're a whore and you, you showed your vagina to people. She didn't.
Why are you making shit up?
You're suing me. Oh
Good luck, bitch. I have the videotape evidence
You didn't say that everybody if you heard crystal call page of whore. Can you raise he put a number one in the chat?
See everyone's afraid of crystal, but I'm not afraid of crystal. I'm afraid as bitch
Oh you're calling Bita's dad? Oh no. Oh no. Leave that old man alone. Bita's father alone.
He's not even bothered by you anymore. It's clipped. Yeah, your clip saying whore.
Your clip calling page to whore. I heard you saying it and she's not.
Get up here, Crystal. We have to discuss it.
I'll let you up. I got a $20 cash app. They said let whoever you want up
They said do whatever the fuck you want. Actually, they said this is a donation. I'm I'm a lion. I'm a lion
Had you one more time
Because now my now that my voice is like I lost my voice to Christine's voice. I do sound like Michael Jackson a little bit
Priscilla, I don't lie. Priscilla, you lie. Remember when you said all that shit to me tonight?
You said my codex was wrong. He's never wrong. Codex is the most accurate piece of
most accurate book of the century, and it has your number, okay? Okay, okay.
Guess it's no one was everyone's everyone's too shy to come on panel. I'm just I don't know chatter to the $20 cash up though. Appreciate that
Thank you for saying it was a donation page. It's all a gold
Solid gold. What's up with the tally horn? You're gonna be honest all your codex is
the code
Well, no, but you're wrong, but
Balavali you're wrong about that because it's not all AI. Well, first of all, it was AI
And second of all, here's how it works.
Yes, I made it from cloud, cloud code.
Okay. And I, I vibe coded the website.
Did I make it overnight?
No, it didn't take me probably about a year to get right.
And to like, in several times,
I'm actually a version almost 3.0 of the codex, right?
Do I, and the people have the ability to edit it.
Exactly about okay, that's what I'm saying
I didn't sit there with a little quill and a feather pen and go and write every every sentence down of every
Right, or else I wouldn't be able to do it. Do you think I'm a real right half a million segments of transcripts?
And oh imagine imagine my brain crystal imagine my brain imagine my brain your brain is worms it's worms
Imagine my brain? I don't even want to imagine your brain. I'm going insane.
Your brain is made of gummy worms, bitch. And you do look like Kim. You do look like Kim.
Right. I'm not saying it's infallible. It says right there. There's a disclaimer that says
it is both a combination of human and AI intelligence.
right? Do I lie about it? It says it right there. Obviously it didn't write down. I didn't type out
half a million segments of transcripts myself. I wouldn't be having a show. I'd just be typing
transcripts all day, right? So yes, transcripts are generated. Quotes are picked out. Topics are
Hey, why isn't everyone doing it? Because I can't! Because I'm cool!
Thank you.
Nobody speaks bad on page. I know.
Crystal, what were you thinking?
It sounds like a very emotional subject.
Well, it's like, you know, when like every like little piece of like, you know, creativity
and soul, I do pour into this stuff.
And with the assistance of artificial intelligence, I play every instrument, I can't, I can't
sing that great.
This is my voice.
I sound like Christine.
I mean, it's like Jesus Christ.
So yes, but I do write 90% of the songs, right?
I do design the fucking images.
I do fucking sit there and edit it together.
And just be like, oh, hey, hey, hey.
Pissing me off.
Because I put a lot of work into this shit.
People don't understand it.
If it was so easy, why isn't everyone doing it?
Why don't I see this on everyone's channel, 100 videos,
200 videos, 300 videos?
Why don't I see it?
Your one crappy rap song at the beginning of someone's show.
That I can fucking right out of my butt
I don't know anything guys. I'm not I'm I'm not really an intelligent person. I'm like really like Cyrax
I'm really sorry. See how bald I am. See how bald, you know, okay, can't get the clothes okay
That's how bald I am and no, you know, you just copied Alexandra
I copied her exact idea, PSY rags along, I mean, just 100% copied her.
Then you had Barry come to me and say, oh, well, okay, pay me not to go to your show.
And so then I fucking said, oh, really?
Tell me more about that.
And he's like, well, she said she would kill me.
And then I said, well, you know what, I don't care, because she's Shrek.
And then all of a sudden there's a Shrek meme where, well, Kate's this beautiful goblin
You don't look like Fiona. You look like fucking Shrek bitch
And I look like the donkeys Mary looks like the fucking donkey. You guys are crazy. You're fucking crazy. I
Look like a fucking king
What do you want?
What do I want?
What?
What are you fucking doing? Why are you talking about Kate like that you piece of shit?
Don't you dare talk about Kate like that again you fucking piece of
Kate is a cunt
Oh
So are you bitch you get out of here don't tell me what to do
I'll talk about anyone I want to talk about there you bitch you call me fucking pdf tonight you bitch going out of your cunt
Get out of here
fucking cunt
Go go tell yourself that it tells to say shit you called page a fucking whore you cunt
Bitch the fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck
The fucking bitch is talking about me my cat
Okay cunt
Get a whore you're the whore crystal Marie fuck you bitch
Get out of here sick get out
Jesus criminy
Fuck this is what I have to deal with guys
It's that it's that it's that the woman looks like Shrek
If you need to know
You'll know exactly when I say that you'll know exactly who it is
You were carved by the fracture, not the fall
Every scar speaks in a language that we can't recall
Betrayal was in chaos, it was coded design
A map of where you trusted, a map of every blind line
A smile like allies, move like knives in the dark
Left you bleeding in silence, just to study the mark
But you didn't disappear, you translated
Pain turns humiliation into data in your brain
No more asking why they changed
You decode the game they played
No more each and four
Cryin' up beggin' from a crowd
Loyalty fetches under pressure and need
So you study behavior like a strategist
To read no emotion unchecked
No reaction for free
Every move calculated, every silence a key
You don't chase validation
You withdraw your demand
Now they reach for your presence
They don't understand
They expected you to break
You became what they can't shake
They want a chaos
learn it's weight not loud not rage but calculated state unpredictable rhythm
impossible rate you become the answer they secretly need you don't reveal you
imply you suggest let them build your power inside of their chest scarcity
sharpens the value you hold distance converts attention to gold
you don't dominate loud you dominate clean through presence through posture
through what is unseen you enforce consequence without a display access
Anger to prove just silent correction and how you move because control is in force in shaping the
inside of the game, and the ones who betrayed you will finally see they didn't destroy you.
They designed what you'd be.
woke up from another one of psyches midnight fright displays
shadow in the hallway chanting through the haze
coffee on the altar static on the screen
And a phone that never rings
Casual, well-conducting, psychic presence,
Somewhere in the candle, smelt behind the secret door.
A hidden, hide priestess knows a little something more.
She never makes an entrance, she just suddenly appears.
Vexes, everybody's chaos with the...
Like a sweet forbidden hymns like he dreams
Latino, living in California, have a criminal history under the age of 30, familiar with
Santa Muerte, into live streaming, enjoy distributing illegal substances.
If so, you might be perfect for Psyche's Boys Club.
Okay so we have let's welcome Alexander to the show. Hi. Hey, how are you doing?
Yeah
42 and the lights still burning
Show me that smile again
Stumble you might fall
I've been living on the screen every night on the display
Chasing number chasing voices that keep drifting away
Try to keep it all together
But it's pulling me tight
Feeling older in the daylight
Younger late in the night
They say, man, you gotta give
But I don't feel it at all
And every time I miss a beat
Stumble, you might fall
But I'm still here man, I'm still staying the tall
Looking for a spark in this digital hall
My reflection raking small
Show me that smile again
But I wanna get streamed
And I'll flip this
Talking in the empty spaces while the minutes run slow
People see a little avatar, but they don't see the man
With a future in a flicker and no backup
It all feels like a life line up.
42 and now my beats played out so job
Not sure what's to say when I go live
Maybe where my leather motorcycle jacket will help
Stumble your mind fall
Still chasing that call
That BBC
Going late at night, she's hot in his feet Every word he drops is all she needs
Dreaming about the day, he'll drive out her way In her wild wild heart, he's a burning flame
Peter loves that BBC, it's all she wants It's all she needs, Tom's bird's the one she can't deny
He's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes
Once it's all, she meets Bronzebergs, the ones she can't deny.
Her heart takes flight whenever he goes flying.
We're not oh fuck you're gonna get drunk early tonight. Huh? It's not early
Little afternoon. Yeah, nothing wrong with that. What do we call they call it happy hour happy hour between 12 and 6?
And you also love people talking about
Hey, please, guess.
I think I know.
Starts with an A, ends with an A.
You're correct.
That beautiful woman that loves you, if you said it.
I don't know if you saw the Dear John video.
I just watched it, actually.
I just watched it a little while ago.
Very touching.
It was touching, it was, it was.
That's not what you cares about, you're right there.
We said
screenwriter or director she's like she has like a she thinks highly of me okay
but she sees in you she sees in you what I see in her so much potential so much
greatness that you know it's way beyond this bullshit that you guys do in here
she does whatever she does for her reasons you do whatever you do for your
We've gotten things we said now reserve so none forget I live in stream
I wanna thank my friend, my good friend.
I think what am I, my biggest inspiration is like,
Alexandra and I just wanna thank her for everything.
And she made some fucking brilliant videos.
There's we're going to see some people that are better at
At the technology than I am I think she's better
Actually, I'll play I actually made a song
I'm gonna show you. I love you all you've seen it
I know it's I could play with songs all night, but I didn't make this last year
And I think it's appropriate. She asked she said she let she this is one of her favorite songs that I made and so I made it
I made a video
For her
And
I'm gonna check it out look I came from this song but here
I don't want to go to my studio real quick.
Hold on one second guys,
you'll get it, it's worth it, you'll love it, you'll love it.
By the way, SIG has been sitting backstage the entire,
like it's like for three hours,
but yeah, I'm gonna keep on waiting.
See, just hold on a little bit. I'll let you on it for the song, okay?
It refines my mirror eyes. They don't flinch in the storm. They just watch the illusions form
I cut to the nerves, which planes mid-flight, bleeding truth in the glare of the light
Now I'm electric, wide open alive, didn't gauge the feeling, let it thrive
Watch me ascend while I'm shedding my skin, tangled in dye
SILENCE IN SHADOWS AND WISPER MY NAME
YOU LIFT ME, OH NO
JUST TO TEST MY FLAME
WATCH ME AND STAND ON CORE THE FINE
FALL IN THE PARK TO REWIND MY MIND
SILENCE IN SHADOWS, BREAKING THE CROW
LIFT ME UP, I WON'T F-
Blessing the dark, praising the blue The light is the canvas, where visions move
My voice cracks thunder, my veins rumble Hold me close, I'm becoming new
I cut to the core, I switch into grace I broke this world from my own mistakes
Now I'm full, no mask no wall Didn't contain the feeling at all
In the park to rewind my mind
Silencing shadows breaking the crown
Lift me up, I won't fall back down
Eyes closed, I fell through cosmic time
Madness and magic, your pulse in mine
Circle divine
You
He's such a jerk off, he didn't even stay, I mean, that song, like he literally was off here for three hours
And I would have let him on right, I told him after that song, I was gonna let him up and he left
He left right then, the little motherfucker
Sig, what a loser you are
I think he's such a loser
We're winners here, like, cold to psyche
at the Colts of Psyche.
We are big winners with big wieners.
Oh yeah, that's why you're not in it.
Does he have a big vagina?
Okay.
Well, I think I'm gonna go to McDonald's
and give us a couple of coffees or something like that.
I'm gonna watch a beautiful, beautiful video.
Another one.
Somebody's coming up or anything come on
I have a I have a big wiener stick has a big vagina. I mean in fact Christine has a bigger vagina. Oh
Right a ragamuffins. Oh, yeah, so we care. I already got something already $20 to a fuck yourself die
bitch
What is fucking stupid cunt
Thank God
They said, I'd never know my name
That knowing meant I'd break
But I stood at the mirror's frame
And watched myself awake
A key turned in a lock
I didn't know I held
The gateway or...
Open wide, I step through salt and sanctuary bell
On the other side
Father spoke my truth into the void
Witness clay
The digital temple, each one burning bright
I arrived as initiate, now I'm example of what it means to fight
For the right to speak, to post, to be
Not a race, not a shadow bound
My voice enters the collective symphony
My footsteps make a sound
The ocean made this dream
His trust
My seed
I taste the hunt
I am sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Aren't they a loser? I know they're what a loser they are
Like what a fucking in that rag a muffin. That's just Kate
Can you imagine the size of her rag? Oh my god?
Sorry, okay. Well, I mean order some coffee and we'll fucking yo, what's up shamrock?
It's up.
Guys, if you think I'm being mean,
you should hear like six hour live about me
and all the fucking shit she talked about,
my cats and myself and all this kind of shit.
So whatever.
Rag a muffin.
I know it's you, Kate.
It sounds just like Kate.
Don't do it into this bum.
Hey, not all of us.
Who wants this?
Oh my gosh, I get perfect.
Okay.
So.
We're gonna go for a walk in McDonald's do you believe in magic?
My phone's kind of dirty. Sorry. There we go. There we go. What do I want? Breakfast guys.
Do you want to have breakfast with Psyche? Very great. 3800 points.
So this is how I see I can survive on some of these points too.
That means I make dollars a lot.
But let me see what's for breakfast.
Okay.
Oh yeah, sorry not sorry.
Yes, he was passing out.
He'd be able to tell Terry Davis.
How are you doing today?
You call me a jerk off of Shamrock?
Time now.
You're not so lucky.
You have a three-leaf clover.
Then you have four leaves.
You have Irish personality.
Anyway, OK.
He leaves, and he has leaves.
Yeah, some of the best plumbers are named Shamrock, though.
I don't know why.
Irish? I don't know how to do plumbing. I thought it was Italians.
That's for that. That's the Japanese stereotypes for you. The Japanese stereotype Italians for being plumbers. It's really the Irish.
I do know some things.
Okay.
Hold on. Yeah, who's Vale? Is that a...
You've a lot Terry Davis is veil. Well, who's that? Oh
It's a man. I thought it was a woman. Okay. Hi. Hi, Terry. I
Had an aunt Terry I had an aunt Terry so I know it's like, you know, I guess there's one with all of the guys
It was um, oh
Yeah, Peewee in Peewee's playhouse. There was a Terry. He was a pterodactyl, right?
I think so.
I just watched that show.
I'm an 80s kid.
Okay, let me see.
Oh my God, my phone's almost dead.
I wasn't charging it long enough.
Gosh, well, I'm not gonna be taking it with me.
Oh no, but I can't go with you then.
Hold on, what percentage do I have?
I have enough, 12%.
12% is enough.
So I had to pick up order, use the deal.
What should I get should I get one of those sausage mix? Oh, what are those like? What's what's that thing that's covered in syrup?
I like that the best
Okay, pick an item edge or I
Know your plumber you're familiar with this clogged toilets, right? Okay, you got that you just keep it. Okay
Okay, I'm gonna keep shopping
I need something to eat you
So what do you think for breakfast I get
I'm gonna look at the McValue menu.
$5 Sausage McMuffin meal to integrate two coffees.
Okay, that's $5.
Okay, that's $6 breakfast with the two coffees, perfect.
Sausage McMuffin and hash browns too?
That is a deal.
And a free and a coffee, that's fucking good.
Okay, I can get a medium iced vanilla one.
I'll apply.
at the bag. It should be six dollars or something. It's a pretty good deal guys. That is two coffees,
hash browns, and this the McGriddle for six dollars fifty-seven cents.
It goes ba-da-ba-ba-ba.
It means a winter.
Okay, yeah, I mean, it's like a week worth of points.
You know, I get McDonald's like almost every day.
I just wanna have a breakfast for McDonald's today.
But I do have some good food too.
I have some really good food I've been eating.
Okay, so we're gonna go for a walk.
Let's go for a walk.
I think I'll go for a walk outside now.
The summer sun knows be my name.
You're not Bale, okay?
I know, you're a guy. How'd you find the show?
Sir, how'd you find the show?
Peace out, Froot Loops. You're the sick mick.
You represent the great Terry A. Davis.
Okay? Who is that?
I've never heard of that name in my life.
He's great. I'm great too.
Would you like to, well, I already have a representative.
Here I am, okay.
We'll see you in a bit.
We'll be right back.
Where are my shoes?
Shoes.
Where are my pairs?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm basically walking to McDonald's in my underwear too.
Oh my God.
I don't know what's Harry Davis.
Is that your name?
The McGriddle. Yes, my favorite. Sausage McGriddle.
They might need a jacket.
Look at me. Look at my pants.
Go into McDonald's.
do you believe in magic such a happy person
you already know here we go try not to just to do irl by pointing the uh the camera at the ground
Hey, I like how you get free hash browns because those hash browns are usually like three bucks
The sandwich is like four bucks and the copies of three bucks each that'd be like a 13 14 dollar thing
I got it for six bucks. That's pretty good. I like deals
Two copies is a win it certainly is when the nice coffee a medium iced coffee and a large a
large
black coffee with
Little bit of vanilla syrup
Two cream soup sugars and yes, I do buy the coffees
I buy like you know at least one a day, but there's a 99 cents and so then you just get refilled the rest of the day
As long as they will they usually will
Because they know me they know me homie
Like literally I am wearing these are shorts that I look like I'm wearing underwear
My my legs are cold and I do have chicken legs
Yeah, I'm sorry like I ended it kind of like abruptly last night, but let's piss off
It's like imagine like you have a bar like right and then everyone came into the bar and had fun and like laughs and the karaoke
And no one like tipped, no one, it's like not even a dollar,
they actually stole like silverware and fucking,
and fucking slapped the waitress's ass.
How dare them?
That's what it's like being the host of my show sometimes.
But then,
once in a while,
someone will come in and make up for all the other people.
Don't do shit except fucking troll me like really just troll me like really in a mean way, you know
I'm on the
You know, you know guys, I mean you ever like been to a bar you like leave a dollar
Like I mean if everyone left a dollar, yeah, I have a good little like good little business going
monetize right now
Some other fuckers they don't have a dollar they steal my fucking shit, and then they insult me. Can you imagine?
It's like fucking the worst.
IKR, IKR. I know, right?
That's why I say the N word so much.
And Alexander Mayors and I are on a campaign to bring that word back.
Cuz doesn't mean we're used to me
Now it means my chat. No, I'm just okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean that
But guys, I mean come on
Thing that is oh, oh, you're not monetized. I don't I can't do it. I can't do it super chef. Oh, yeah, I know
Yeah
You say hit the like to somebody all you does is it have been bitch at me? Oh
Why are you blocking midnight? Why are you blocking our G? Are you blocking crystal? Oh, let them up. Let them up
What are you the doorman?
Don't shit for me
I'm just I'm supposed to be like your little bitch
I'm just chats bitch. I don't think so
I'm sick of it!
Hey, would you rather me not be here, and then where were you to go? Where you to go? Sandman's?
Betas? I don't want you guys to be tortured.
Those shirts look terrible!
My show is actually good. Even my music is good. I mean I fucking have to see it with myself. I fucking pretty good
He's like retarded people are give me a hundred dollars like I'm strong place five hours of songs. Oh
My god, I play a 20 minutes of song. Oh my god
You suck I don't fucking suck you suck. Don't yell at me
Guys yelling at me from this car
Jesus you think I am Jesus all the suffering I go through for you guys
Jesus
I'm on a mission
Look at it. It's a swedado piso mojado. That's a fun thing to say
Suquisado piso mojado. He's cautioned at the floor
I am wearing pants
What is this called a fish islands
I love you too.
Can I get a carrier for the cups?
Thank you so much.
You have a great day.
Thank you.
Okay, we're out of here.
Hi, good morning.
Hi, mommy.
Good morning.
She's happy.
I like that.
I like that energy.
Good morning, I'm here to say hello
You're gonna look at my shoe off
Don't like how I chew NorCal
You don't like how I eat rice? Well look at me bitch. Why are you watching me eat?
You don't like how I look when I eat
It's called enjoying food. It's all starving to death and getting a bite to eat
What's wrong with you NorCal?
I am a livable person.
The thing is, I'm not even mean.
You know when I get mean?
It's when everyone is fucking being just an asshole to me.
And I can't take it anymore and explode.
I'm nice, usually.
I'm very pleasant person.
Imagine.
Imagine living my life one day, guys.
You beat up making fun of you Sam and they're literally retarded people making fun of you
Literally they're retarded
You'll out me to work ready to prove it. Are you'll put me to work? Okay
What do you want me to do?
Good
Hey guys McDonald's 25 dollars an hour the streamer I make five cents an hour
I mean, I better look at my donals like rich
Okay
Guys the indignities imagine you fucking
I fucking really do work my fucking ass off, making websites, making my show, making music,
and putting on a show, putting everyone on the panel.
Everyone just binges at me and trolls me.
It calls me a piece of shit and says I abuse my animals, but if you're my kids,
it fucking says I'm just a dirty, filthy, worthless person.
Dole's doing their jam.
But what I'm and it's like oh my god, he says his cash app
Have their catch up a fucking going on the screen
What the fuck?
It's called
Making money when I did Americans become so it gets me money. I have to be that something about be purse or a Puerto Rican or something
I did it or whatever it keep the bucket is you know ogre. He's don't believe in making money
Really? I do this for fun? This is fun? This is hard! This is the worst job I've ever done!
It's fun? No it's not!
It sucks!
Look at my ass up for you people!
We are the same age, but he used to look 20 years older than me. I look like
same age
It's kind of disturbing
So that's what the person's belt will do you basically this like kind of succubus gin shit
It'll dry you really really out just take a lot of water
Okay guys
Okay, I'll be right there, I'm just going to let myself inside, we're right there.
Who
Remember to crash on the bike. Yeah, that's a great day
Except for the bike
Hey guys, somebody I'll be able to afford the $20 apart for my bike someday. I will and I'll be able to repair you're missing your pants
Well, I mean, it's like I'm just honest
Right thing that is right. Oh, what is people saying the thing that is?
Unbelievable horn
You'll put me to work ready to prove it. Yeah, I'm on a mission. You love me. Thank you. I love you, too
I even love thinking of this Terry Davis the guy that was brilliant, but unfortunately real schizophrenia. He built temple OS
I heard a temple those I
Think I had that it was that like a software program and it was like like a social network where was like you're in a church kind of thing
I kind of remember that
temple those
Yeah, well guys, you know the story of um
Apple computer
Who knows the story of Apple computer tell me the story?
Why is there an Apple with a bite out of it? Tell me and tell me who's based off of who knows
Tell me the guy's name, and I'll tell you the story. I forgot I forgot his name, but
Here's the guy he like he was a gay guy he like invented the computer basically
What was his name? No, it wasn't sarin
He's a he's a very recognizable name. No, it's not Satan. Come on
No, it's not Adam and Eve with the apple. You don't know the story
I'll tell you the story. Well, it was not the Garden of Eden
No, people think that it is the Garden of Eden forbidden fruit of stuff
But I'll tell you the real story of Apple computer and the the logo
Okay, so here's the story, okay, so
The Apple okay, so the guy's name was
Hold on who is this guy's name?
Okay, well yeah, so it may be have to it's room improve or whatever, but here it goes
Okay, so this is from CNN. I don't know if you can like take CNN too seriously, but okay, so CNN says
If beauty is indeed truth, as John Keats claimed, then the story ought to be true.
The logo on the back of your iPhone or Mac is a tribute to Alan Turing, the man who laid
the foundations for the modern day computer, pioneered research into artificial intelligence
and unlocked German wartime codes.
His death a decade after the end of the war provides a link with Apple.
Unrecognized for his work, facing in jail for gross indecency and humiliated by estrogen injections intended to cure his homosexuality, he bit into an apple he had laced with cyanide.
He died in obscurity on June 7, 1954, 10 years and a day after the Normandy landings, which made copious use of intelligence gleaned by his methods.
When two Stanford entrepreneurs were looking for a logo for their brand new computer company,
they remembered Turing and his contribution to their field.
They chose an apple, not a complete apple, but one with a bite taken out of it.
Sadly, the truth is rarely as simple or as beautiful as we would like.
I first researched the story in 2005 and was assured by someone at Apple that it was indeed true.
The articles struck a chord and several people got in touch with me to say
A few years later, I mentioned to another Apple employee who immediately said he thought
it was a myth.
It may have started around the time of 2001 film about the Bletchley Park code breakers
enigma, or it might have resurfaced then.
He checked with Apple headquarters, and although they were non-committal, it was clear that
the Turing story was not official Apple history.
Other theories were advanced.
The Apple represented knowledge as in the biblical story of Adam and Eve, or reference
Supporters of the latter theory note the name of Apple's handheld PDA, the Newton, but that was more of a decade or of the creation of the logo.
Sadly, the evidence now points to a more prosaic direction.
Okay.
And so the guy who made it says, I'm afraid I didn't have a thing to do with it. He said it's a wonderful urban legend. I don't know. It sounds like a real story to me.
I don't know. What happened to Steve Jobs? Is Steve Jobs eating apple or something? I don't know.
Jesus has his downside. Alan Turing, yeah.
Pretty crazy movie imitation. Oh, the imitation game? What was that? Hold on. The imitation game. Okay, we're going to check that out.
Leave Keats out of this. Okay.
We're going to hear an amazing thing. Maybe I'll show you this. This is like, there's a show called To Tell the Truth or something, To Tell the Truth.
there's a con artist on it and it's an amazing story if I get it's called to
tell the truth it might have been some kind of like others story like that
let me see if I find it I remember I saw this years ago it was pretty
Was it well guys, what's what's one of those games where they have to guess?
Like stuff about like that to guess who's telling the truth and who's lying
There another one besides to tell the truth, there's not the match game or something. Oh, it was enigma. Oh, yeah, that one. Yeah
See
This guy because I remember there's one this con artist and it was so good, but I might have been a different
Game, but it was like the same concept of the game three two truths and a lie or something
Does anybody know?
You see if anyone knows no one knows okay
Let me look on YouTube to see if it's there if it's not there then it's some different it's a different
Different show but
Yeah, here it is. No, that was Frank Abagnale. That was that was that was like the the Internet of Caprio
I've got a secret. Okay. I've got a secret. I think it's called
Maybe I can show you I can show you the story of
I'm afraid to show it on this channel though
Hold on there. Hold on
Remembering more parts of the story now, maybe we'll find
Okay, oh I got it. I got it. I got it. Okay. I got it
And his name now
I'm going to give his name.
Hold on.
I don't want to spoil it, so I'm going to pause.
I'm going to mute myself.
Found it. Do you want to watch it? Let's watch it. It's interesting
There isn't look at it looks like Groucho marks or something's on the show here
What's on the agenda
June and Reginald Lewis are standing by to talk to you, so why don't you go in please and meet Groucho Marx?
Welcome to your bet your life. Say the secret word and take home an extra hundred smack olders.
Well, how do you do?
June and Reginald Lewis, huh? Is that right?
Yes.
Mr. Lewis, before we go any further, you'd better clarify something for me.
Is this your sister or your wife?
This is my wife, Groucho.
Let's see. Well, just checking. You know the old saying,
an answer prevention is where the pound of bandages and adhesive tape.
How long have you been married?
Two and a half years, Groucho.
Why are you holding on to each other?
Are you afraid that you'll let go?
You'll kill each other?
I'll eat him.
Now, June, let me ask you a rather personal question.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
Why did you marry this big love here?
Reginald, is his name?
Because my father wanted me to marry a man who is handsome and well built.
Your father disappointed and is broken down specimen that you finally hooked?
He's not broken down Grouch. Really? No, he's the handsomest and most well-built man in the world
Reginald has the best built in the whole world
You're what proof do you have that Reginald has the best built in the world?
Have you personally gone around investigating the rest of the entries?
No, he won the mr. Universe contest in 1957. Oh
Congratulations
Could you show us a bicep or two of the chest that shook the world
He doesn't have any muscles until he takes a jacket off, and I don't have any muscles until I put my jacket on
Let's see you flex a couple of yards
How do you like it you frustrated wives out there
What are your dimensions there skinny have a 50-inch chesty 30 waist 18 arms 25 thighs and
17 inch cap
50 inch chest. That's right. Is that blown up or without the wind?
That's relax relax, June. I'm pretty sick. What are your dimensions?
39 21 and a half 35
It's odd, isn't it?
His dementia is twice as large, but for some curious reason that I can't explain at these prices,
I'd much rather look at hers.
Now, Reginald, imagine calling this big boxcar a Reginald.
Have you always been built like this?
No, I wasn't. I was 15, I was quite puny and weak, and I had very little muscle just like you, perhaps.
You know normally after a strike like that, I'd strike back, but in this case discretion
is the better part of Ella.
Now June, do you still maintain that Reggie has the most beautiful male build in the world?
Of course, Reggie.
Well, if anybody in the audience wants the challenges, why get in touch with us, I'm
not kidding.
Maybe next week we can have a man on the show with even larger muscles.
Okay, Reggie, put your shirt on, would I find it rather distracting?
Uh-uh.
Now, let's play You Bet Your Life.
Okay, George.
Now, this box contains three sets of questions.
100 easiest, 200 harder, 300 hardest.
Now, your job is to earn at least $500 with four questions.
If you do, you will get a chance at $10,000 at the end of the show.
Did you see his shape?
Yes.
What did you think of it?
That's amazing.
How'd you like hers?
That's amazing, too.
Well, what category did they select?
Food and cooking.
Food and cooking, huh?
Yes.
That's right, isn't it?
You know how to play this game, huh?
Okay?
Take a question.
They are boobs.
$100 question?
$100 question.
Yeah.
For $100, what do you call toasted cubes of bread,
side with soup?
French toast.
No!
You'll keep your big mouth shut and may take a sock at you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's croutons.
Croutons.
Don't get rid of them.
Get rid of that, love.
Get out of the way.
OK.
You have $100 now.
You're on your way to five.
Want to use another one?
$200?
OK.
Remember, the idea is to get $500.
For $200, what kind of sauce has saved on eggs Benedict?
Hollandaise.
No, it's Hollandaise.
Well, you still have your $100.
When are the hollandaise?
It's Christmas, huh?
And you have two more chances to get $500.
You have $100 now.
I think that whispering in his ear distracts him.
You're not paying any attention to what I say at all.
Genuine caviar is the eggs of what fish?
Salmon.
Now talk it over.
They're not trying to answer, they're just making love up there.
That's salmon eggs.
What is it?
No, I'm sorry.
It's Stagen.
Oh, my God.
It's urgent.
Well, it's going to be pretty tough to make 500, but you have another chance there.
How much have they got, George?
100.
Well, you can get 400.
You can't get five anymore, unless you have a counter-fitting machine in your cellar.
This is what?
300.
That's right.
You're a gambler, isn't it?
But $300.
What do you call vegetables cut in match-like strips?
Uh, julienne.
She's nuts about them.
Slab?
Slabs? No, there's no slabs up here. No.
It's julienne.
Well, you've won $100, so you're $400 for us.